<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SwitchToVanillaTitle">SWITCH TO CLASSIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SwitchToVanillaDescription">Switch to classic version of the game</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GalaxyRingTitle">Galaxy Ring</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GalaxyRingDescription">A galaxy rotating around a big black hole like a giant circle of stars.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_OUTGAME" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionNameHarTitle">HARMONY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionNameHarmonyDescription">A faction of sentient minerals, trapped by Dust in this galaxy</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionHarDescription">Home Planet Type: Tundra
Diplomatic Alignment: Neutral
Gameplay: Exploration and Isolationist
Main Victory Type: Wonder/Population
 
The Harmony has been sentient since the dawn of time in the known universe. A fundamental creature born of the energies of the Big Bang, the living rocks of the Harmony are capable of manipulating quantum energies and gravitation. Their mineral nature means that they are closely attuned to planets and rocks across the galaxy; they have an unparalleled ability to identify and exploit natural resources and anomalies. Factions that ally with them share in this unique ability, and those that choose to fight them will find them difficult to dislodge once they have settled in.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense05NormTitle">Solid Citizens</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense05NormDescription">Fewer troops and civilians are lost during a land invasion</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy11NormTitle">Strategically Resourceful</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy11NormDescription">Gains Monopoly on Strategic Resources with only 3 deposits</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy12NormTitle">Mineral Memory</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy12NormDescription">Can see all Strategic Resources of visited systems</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy13NormTitle">Efficient Stock</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy13NormDescription">Increases the FIS generation per Strategic Resource deposit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy14NormTitle">Lap of luxury</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy14NormDescription">Luxury bonus is increased by half</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy14AltTitle">Asceticism</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy14AltDescription">Luxury bonus is divided by half</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero05NormTitle">Dust congruity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero05NormDescription">Heroes leech 30% Dust of systems they are orbiting</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTitle">Harmony Affinity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyDescription">Provides a basic set of faction traits similar to the Harmony (Population, Resources Exploitation)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityEmperorDescription">Provides a basic set of faction traits similar to the Sheredyn (Economic/Military, Industrial Exploitation)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityMappingHarmonyTitle">Harmony Appearance</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityMappingHarmonyDescription">Your custom faction will display the 2D and 3D visuals of the Harmony.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_FACTION" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UniquePlanetsTitle">Unique planets</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UniquePlanetsDescription">Click to toggle on or off the existence of Unique Planets in the game.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Temple16Title">TEMPLE OF THE STUDIOUS GUARD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Temple16Description">Having studied sociology, anthropology, and psychology in unimaginable depth, a group of researchers founded this institute to further their knowledge. The wisdom contained in its records helps a leader to track, understand, predict, and control the sympathies of their subjects.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Temple16TooltipEffect1">25% ḗ ON PLANET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_OPTIONS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetEndlessWonder09Title">#EAB643#Husk of Knowledge#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetEndlessWonder09Description">Auriga housed the greatest site for the study of xenobiology ever created by the genius of the Endless. A towering achievement of industry and science, the surface and crust of the planet were a warren of laboratories, biospheres, and research centers. When the bombs fell during the Dust Wars, this enormous installation became the greatest expanse of ruins -- and store of lost knowledge -- in the known galaxy. Should the laboratories ever be repaired and the data recovered, the scientific benefit would be unimaginable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetEndlessWonder09RestorationTitle">#EAB643#Husk of Knowledge#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetEndlessWonder09RestorationDescription">Auriga housed the greatest site for the study of xenobiology ever created by the genius of the Endless. A towering achievement of industry and science, the surface and crust of the planet were a warren of laboratories, biospheres, and research centers. When the bombs fell during the Dust Wars, this enormous installation became the greatest expanse of ruins -- and store of lost knowledge -- in the known galaxy. Should the laboratories ever be repaired and the data recovered, the scientific benefit would be unimaginable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_GEN" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_GAMEMENU" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleBomberCategoryTitle">SPECIAL MODULE (BOMBERS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleFighterCategoryTitle">SPECIAL MODULE (FIGHTERS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleTroopsCategoryTitle">SPECIAL MODULE (TROOPS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModulePointDefenseCategoryTitle">SPECIAL MODULE (POINT DEFENSE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombPopulationCategoryTitle">SUPPORT MODULE (BOMBS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombImprovementCategoryTitle">SUPPORT MODULE (BOMBS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialSlotsCost"> SLOTS: $Slot</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarTooltipDefenseShelterFromInvasionTitle">DEFENSE SHELTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarTooltipDefenseShelterFromInvasionFormat">$Value%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarTooltipDefenseAntiAircraftFromInvasionTitle">ANTI AIRCRAFT DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarTooltipDefenseAntiAircraftFromInvasionFormat">$Value%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TOOLTIP" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombTitle">BOMBING RUN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombDescription">Bomb the star system this fleet is orbiting</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombInvalidDescription">Cannot bomb: you are not equipped with bombs to damage this star system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombOwnSystemDescription">Cannot bomb: this is one of your star systems</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombSystemNotEnoughInvasionStrengthDescription">Cannot bomb: you do not have enough fighters and bombers providing land invasion strength</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombNeutralSystemDescription">Cannot bomb: this is a neutral star system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombNoOrbitDescription">Cannot bomb: your fleet must be orbiting a star system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombLockedSystemDescription">Cannot bomb: the star system is locked by an ongoing battle</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombAlreadyDescription">Cannot bomb: you have already performed an action with your fleet on this star system this turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombSystemNotUnderSiegeDescription">Cannot bomb: the star system is not under siege</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlBombFallbackDescription">Cannot bomb</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionTitle">INSTANTANEOUS INVASION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionDescription">Try to immediately invade the star system this fleet is orbiting by sending land troops.
 
Success Probability: #33CDFF#$Value %#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionInvalidDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: you have no troops available in your fleet</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionOwnSystemDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: this is one of your star systems</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionNeutralSystemDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: this is a neutral star system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionNoOrbitDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: your fleet must orbit a star system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionLockedSystemDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: the star system is locked by an ongoing battle</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionAlreadyDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: you have already performed an action with your fleet on this star system this turn.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionSystemNotUnderSiegeDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously: the star system is not under siege</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetControlLandInvasionFallbackDescription">Cannot invade instantaneously</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ControlBannerEmpireHarmonyTaxFormat">$Tax% CONVERSION RATE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HarmonyBannerAcademyDisabledDescription">The Harmony do not see any interest in hiring mercenaries corrupted by Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HarmonyChangeHeroDisabledDescription">The Harmony have no need for managing Dust-corrupted mercenaries.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairTitle">REPAIR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairDescription">Click this button to repair the selected ships</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_GALAXY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TradeRoutesFoodGeneratedDescription">Click this button to sort trade routes by food production.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TradeRoutesIncomeHarmonyDescription">The Food and Science incomes generated by your trade routes with a specific empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireVariableTaxRateHarmonyTitle">MIND AND MATTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireVariableTaxRateHarmonyDescription">The mental resources of the Harmony can be oriented towards creating more of their kind or towards studying the technology of the galaxy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_EMPIRE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CantBuyoutConsiderSystemIndustry">You cannot buyout this item: special improvement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemVariableStackedOverProductionDescription">This is the "stacked" industry value . Industrial overproduction remaining at the end of the turn is stacked. The stacked industry is capped at 5x a system’s industry (up to 7x with the proper technology). A multiplier is applied to the stacked industry, allowing it to increase slightly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_SYSTEM" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_RESEARCH" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UniquePlanetAurigaTitle">AURIGA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UniquePlanetAurigaDescription">Now a dead, lifeless planet, the husk of Auriga contains an unequalled wealth of Endless ruins.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_PLANET" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementTrade1HarmonyTitle">EXTREME OPTION EXCHANGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementTrade1HarmonyDescription">Previously, option trading was a straightforward if technical calculation based on Black-Scholes and similar pricing models. However, with the inclusion of relativistic and non-relativistic frames these calculations become terrifically complex; any star system that can build the sophisticated computing and trading systems needed to deal in these options gains substantial benefits.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueHarmonyTitle">RESTORATION GRIDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueHarmonyDescription">Minerals are known for their unusual affinity for and reaction to certain forms of waves. When a planet is fully "harmonized", the living minerals of the Harmony can instigate a form of particle vibration that coheres the citizens and their daily activities via a system-wide series of grids. The primary role of these grids is to restore a part of the powers that the Harmony lost when they encountered Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueEmperorTitle">DEPLOYMENT NETWORK</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueEmperorDescription">Deployment can be materials, supplies, or people. To move them maximum distances at minimum cost requires networks that run in straight lines from point to point. While this creates enormous savings and profits, it also redirects money and land from other uses and upsets those who had inconveniently placed back yards.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementFood1HarmonyTitle">SILIC SOILS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementFood1HarmonyDescription">The Harmony are unlike other peoples, including in their dietary needs. While they learn to turn living matter into energy forms that provide sustenance, that process is accelerated when there are higher proportions of silicates in the soil. In guiding agricultural exploitation in this direction, they can efficiently improve food production.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementHabitat4AutomatonTitle">ORBITAL SUPERSTRUCTURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementHabitat4AutomatonDescription">The size of orbital platforms was previously limited by variables like orbital distance, gravity, and solar exposure. However, technologies learned from other civilizations have permitted the Automatons to make larger, more densely populated orbitals with greater efficiency and higher output.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToDustTerranTitle">ADVANCED DUSTGEN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToDustTerranDescription">Dust can be generated by trade or by fabrication. In this case, enormous containment systems of stimulated Dust can slowly process any physical input into more of this precious substance. The science behind it, for the moment, is not understood, but the results speak for themselves.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToScienceSophonTitle">LOW-IMPACT LABS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToScienceSophonDescription">Ecologically designed, virtual, advanced scientific laboratories can be built using nothing more than enormous computer capacity and a willing mind. With few requirements for energy and materials, these can be an extraordinarily efficient way to do research.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToFoodHarmonyTitle">ELEMENTAL REDUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToFoodHarmonyDescription">As the Harmony familiarize themselves with the tools and resources of industry, they come to realize that there is unexpected value the items that are created. By converting production chains to generate certain types of finished products, they can create supplies that provide the emanations upon which the Harmony feed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToFoodSowerTitle">TECH CROP FARMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToFoodSowerDescription">A highly specialized form of agriculture, unwanted or surplus output from industrial systems can be used as raw material inputs to these specialized farms that generate Sower foods.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionScienceToDustEmperorTitle">ADVANCED APP LABS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionScienceToDustEmperorDescription">The idea behind these labs is to get advanced technology into the hands of consumers in the form of useful products. As a trickle-down from the military research programs, many high-tech military discoveries can be turned into profitable trade goods.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionDustToScienceSophonTitle">SUPRA-QUANTIC COMPUTING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionDustToScienceSophonDescription">Ingredients: Stimulated Dust, solar energy, planet-scale processing complexes of tunneled quantum computers. Directions: Combine, and await results as knowledge advances at a blistering speed. Caution: Remain at 2 light-years distance (minimum).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovingTradeRoutesGainAmoebaTitle">RESOURCES PLATFORM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovingTradeRoutesGainAmoebaDescription">This vast and complex structure handles not only commercial transactions that involve the many strange products of the galaxy, but also has the infrastructure needed to test, preserve, package, and ship them. Auction houses, stasis systems, labs, spaceports and groundports, and merchant offices are all examples of what is created in this enormous project.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemRecycleTitle">DECON DROIDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemRecycleDescription">In the service of a brutal but sometimes necessary maneuver, the entire infrastructure of a planet can be broken down and sold off. Rather than the use of bombs or other destructive devices, these robots use applied deconstruction technologies to revert useful materials into their basic elements.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemRazeTitle">PLASMA RAZE GRID</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemRazeDescription">Whether the result of an impetuous colonization decision or an impending attack, sometimes everything on a planet must be destroyed and the population removed. Once the civilians are in a colony ship, a series of plasma generators placed around the planet can be triggered to blast all surface installations into ash.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TECHSYSTEM" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetaryImprovementStrategicResource1Title">STRATEGICAL ROCK</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetaryImprovementStrategicResource1Description">Increases by one the strategic resource deposit size generated by the planet when the improvement is used.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TECHPLANET" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA26EmperorTitle">QUANTUM PROCESSING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA26EmperorDescription">While the theory of quantum computing is ancient, the mechanical difficulties of preparing a physical machine with the appropriate number of qubits (roughly 10^7) meant that it was a practical impossibility. Now that civilization has reached the point where its technology is capable of this, a boom in the solution of exceedingly complex problems is taking place.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA37AutomatonTitle">STASIS CONTAINMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA37AutomatonDescription">The ability to "stack" unneeded industrial capacity as various forms of materials and potential energy is a great advantage for the Automatons. With the use of cutting-edge stasis systems, this ability can be further increased.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA38EmperorTitle">PRIVATIZED RESEARCH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA38EmperorDescription">As a largely military society, enormous advances in science often occur in military or governmental labs. Now that the need for money to fund expansion is increasing, agencies are created specifically to develop commercial applications for military technology.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA39SophonTitle">AUGMENTED VIRTUALIZATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA39SophonDescription">Industry is practical, but to the Sophon mind it is over-emphasized. In fact, many day-to-day objects and actions can be efficiently virtualized, freeing up resources and minds to focus on more important things.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT55SowerTitle">ARTIFICIAL BIOLOGICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT55SowerDescription">Plants are amazing factories for converting water and soil into more complex systems. Though it requires years of study and manipulation, Sower scientists can create plant species that break down and re-convert scrap materials into energy sources.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE04HarmonyTitle">EFFICIENT SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE04HarmonyDescription">By augmenting the natural magnetic characteristics of the hull material and using lighter alloys in construction, this improved ship design gives bonuses to tonnage and improves kinetic and missile defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE04HarmonyTitle">EFFICIENT SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE04HarmonyDescription">By augmenting the natural magnetic characteristics of the hull material and using lighter alloys in construction, this improved ship design gives bonuses to tonnage and improves kinetic and missile defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE06HarmonyTitle">APPLIED CASIMIR EFFECT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE06HarmonyDescription">After decades of experimentation with plates of the right size, material, and distance, the vacuum energy created through the quantum mechanics of the Casimir Effect can finally be exploited as an energy source.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE08HarmonyTitle">BARYONIC SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE08HarmonyDescription">While there are some particles that can pass through plasma shielding, this improved version prevents penetration by any baryon particle (primarily neutrons and protons).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE11HarmonyTitle">ATMOSPHERIC FILTRATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE11HarmonyDescription">A first step in purifying and preparing planets for colonization or terraforming consists of reducing toxic elements in the atmosphere and creating tolerable chemical balances. Recent scientific advances mean that these processes can also be applied to gas giants.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE14HarmonyTitle">APPLIED ATMOSPHERICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE14HarmonyDescription">A great deal of practical engineering for ships can be learned from atmospheric sciences. In particular, streamlined and efficient ventilation systems as well as more advanced magnetic and thermodynamic models all aid in creating next-generation ships </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE16HarmonyTitle">NON-BARYONIC SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE16HarmonyDescription">Non-baryonic particles had long been the great mystery of advanced physics. Now, a greater understanding of the nature and mechanics of particles such as photons, gravitons, and anti-matter permits the creation of shielding systems that either repel or contain non-baryonic matter.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE19HarmonyTitle">PERSONAL FIELDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE19HarmonyDescription">By lowering the power requirements and toxicity of shields, and increasing their efficiency, it is possible to develop shields on a level that they can be worn by individuals and used to block radiation, noise, and light. The technology can logically be extended to do advanced insulation of any size environment.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE26HarmonyTitle">DARK ENERGY EFFECTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE26HarmonyDescription">The mastery of non-baryonic matter is a great advance for science which would not be possible without mastery of complex mathematical models and their associated physical systems. Wave and particle effects propagated through dark energy can have ripple effects on a solar system level, effecting all forms of matter therein.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE32AmoebaTitle">CONDENSATE SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE32AmoebaDescription">Originating on an Ocean planet, the Amoeba have a natural tendency to prefer water environments. In order to simplify the process of Ocean terraforming, a group of scientists created a way to accelerate the conversion of frozen asteroids into viable, liquid water.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE33AutomatonTitle">SHORT-RANGE ENTANGLEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE33AutomatonDescription">This major development in galactic technology was the result of a lab accident involving Automatons nicknamed Alice and Bob, a bell, and a few qubits in strongly nonclassical superposition states.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE34SwarmTitle">EXTREME EXTRACTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE34SwarmDescription">Recent technological advances allow post-depletion resource extraction. While the planet becomes toxic and ruined, the additional resources can be used to improve ship effectiveness.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE35ResistanceTitle">ENDLESS LEVERAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE35ResistanceDescription">The devotion of the Pilgrims to the relics and ruins of the Endless is not merely conceptual. Every installation that they uncover brings them closer to understanding this lost civilization, and the accumulation of this knowledge grows exponentially as more mysteries are unveiled.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE36ResistanceTitle">NULL-G FIELDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE36ResistanceDescription">This is a point in the physical sciences where the border between math and reality disappears. The ability to create static fields that operate independent of gravitons would not be possible without concepts and technologies borrowed from the Endless.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE38SophonTitle">ADAPTIVE ECOLOGIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE38SophonDescription">Though mentally adventurous, Sophons are not physically daring. To ease their society into space travel and extraplanetary settlement, research must be done to adapt familiar Sophon biospheres to various hostile environments.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE39SowerTitle">SOCIOLOGICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE39SowerDescription">It is strange for a machine culture to worry about things like community and approval, but as the Sowers expand this becomes a necessity. The science of Sociologics, dedicated to improving relations between Sower entities - grouped or individual - is now a necessity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE40SowerTitle">TUNDRA GEOMORPHOLOGY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE40SowerDescription">As machine beings, the study of terraforming was only of peripheral interest to the Sowers. However, the discovery that the Endless most likely originated on a Tundra planet has driven the Sowers to delve deeply into the sciences of Tundra terraforming.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE41HarmonyTitle">RESOURCE LEVERAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE41HarmonyDescription">Tuned to the rhythms of the galaxy, the Harmony are far more efficient at finding and exploiting lodes of Strategic Resources. By linking the living crystal of their ships to the Harmony's own minds, Harmony vessels can also sense the shapes of the galaxy and 'feel' the locations of planets and systems that contain useful resources.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT01HarmonyTitle">SOIL XENOBIOLOGY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT01HarmonyDescription">Studies of soil samples from other planets plus advances in understanding of extremophilic bacteria permit scientists to create, under certain conditions, hardier and more productive crops.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT02HarmonyTitle">XENOLOGY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT02HarmonyDescription">First contacts with alien beings cause a rapid development in disparate branches of study - linguistics, anthropology, biology, sociology. These are quickly brought together under the unifying title of "xenology."</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT02EmperorTitle">XENOLOGY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT02EmperorDescription">First contacts with alien beings cause a rapid development in disparate branches of study - linguistics, anthropology, biology, sociology. These are quickly brought together under the unifying title of "xenology."</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT03HarmonyTitle">PARTICLE SCANNING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT03HarmonyDescription">Early advances in systems that capture signatures from particles--be they matter or anti-matter--permit simple 'scanners' that poll space-time for any activity--even neutrino, photon and graviton. This information is used to find, identify, and track all objects that will enter or exit a planetary system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT04HarmonyTitle">RELATIVISTIC ECONOMICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT04HarmonyDescription">The effect of time dilation and space travel on traditional financial models is non-negligible. This new branch of economics provides a basis for defining investment and profit under non-Newtonian physics in non-Euclidean space-time, e.g. observed interest rates, human capital erosion, and NPV (Net Proto-Heisenberg Value).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT05HarmonyTitle">BOTANICAL SCANNING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT05HarmonyDescription">Being relatively sedentary and slow-growing, plants are easier to scan and analyze than animals. Systems to tag and scan plant life on a large scale aid immeasurably in efforts to detoxify and colonize new planets and systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT06HarmonyTitle">IMPROVED FLEET MANAGEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT06HarmonyDescription">The complexities of managing a fleet are enormous, and more so when the problems of time, distance, and communication stretch across a galaxy. Systems of Command, Control, and Communications that move at the speed of thought are necessary, and would likely not be possible without a rudimentary understanding of Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT07HarmonyTitle">RELATIVISTIC MARKETS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT07HarmonyDescription">The value of a good or service has traditionally depended on simple, two-dimensional models involving supply and demand. However, the ability to move through space-time in unusual ways requires re-thinking of traditional market structures and commodity pricing. Without these forms of advanced, 'hard' economic theory, interstellar trade remains a risky game of chance. With them, it remains a slightly less risky game of chance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT08HarmonyTitle">PLANETARY LANDSCAPING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT08HarmonyDescription">In order to further control the environment and resources of a planet, landscaping can be done on a scale that is almost like re-terraforming. This permits far more intensive use of the surface for agriculture, development, or other purposes. In order to monitor and maintain a more delicate ecological balance, however, industry tends to be minimized.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT09HarmonyTitle">XENOMINEROLOGY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT09HarmonyDescription">It is not merely alien races, planets, and stars that are strange, it is the metals and minerals themselves that are discovered 'out there.' Xenominerology' is the study of the many forms of metal and mineral that can exist in the universe, their myriad properties and uses, and an understanding of their monetary value.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT10HarmonyTitle">NANOSCALE THERMODYNAMICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT10HarmonyDescription">Thermodynamic systems are essentially simple circuits of absorption, transport, convection, and condensation. To do this on the level of atoms and molecules is something else, however. A capacity to create nano- and pico-scale units that heat and refrigerate is a game-changer. No pun intended.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT12HarmonyTitle">QUANTUM COMMUNICATIONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT12HarmonyDescription">While the magic of neutrino communications and quantum tunneling did not turn out quite as expected, the exploitation of other aspects of relativity have permitted the creation of lag-less communications across space and time. While the math cannot be explained by less than forty-two Earth years of study, it has been proved that polarity-inverted time-reversed anti-messages are highly effective, with the loss of the occasional punctuation mark.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT13HarmonyTitle">INTER-SPECIES HR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT13HarmonyDescription">The famous saying of the Amoeba: "One being's slavery is another being's public welfare plan" certainly applies here. The knowledge of where the fine lines are between different alien species and their definitions of slavery, exploitation, and hard work are of enormous importance to future galactic entrepreneurs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT15HarmonyTitle">ALIEN BARTER THEORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT15HarmonyDescription">Many things influence the outcome of a negotiation--what the other wants, who influences them, how important it is, etc. Every alien race has different values, beliefs, and assumptions; studying these beforehand provides an enormous advantage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT16HarmonyTitle">ADVANCED BIOLOGICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT16HarmonyDescription">Biologics — drugs made through a biological process rather than chemical synthesis, a category that includes recombinant proteins, vaccines, and antibodies — are the fastest-growing segment of the pharmaceutical industry</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT19HarmonyTitle">FUTURISTIC GAME THEORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT19HarmonyDescription">Game theory is a complex subject dealing with independent agents, choice, probability, and forecasting. Improved understanding of potential and probable outcomes means that many options and decisions can be considered, even if they were previously considered uncertain or even hazardous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT22HarmonyTitle">NEURAL NET SOCIETY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT22HarmonyDescription">Far beyond simple networked computers that talk to networked appliances and personal information technologies lies the possibility of what is, more or less, a networked everything. Movement, consumption, creation, and development are all done by entities--living or not--that can be networked to create a seamlessly perfect execution of any function necessary in a society.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT23HarmonyTitle">ACCELERATED EVOLUTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT23HarmonyDescription">Based on the ancient technologies of recombinant gene engineering, accelerated evolution is a pool of techniques that overall permit organisms to adapt and thrive at an very rapid pace. When applied to crops, it produces densely packed fields of disease- and pest-resistant plants that self-fertilize, adapt to intense climate conditions, and even taste good.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT24HarmonyTitle">PERFECT FORECASTING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT24HarmonyDescription">As better understanding of the technology behind Dust drives computing power close to infinity, there is almost no limit to the number of variables that can be included in an estimation -- and the accuracy of the associated predictions moves close to perfection. Careful manipulation of events, media, and key personalities can be done in order to always have, for instance, exceedingly favorable poll results.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT26HarmonyTitle">DIRECTED AI COMPUTING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT26HarmonyDescription">Academics came up with a mouthful of words for this simple concept: researchers partnering with an advanced AI to improve their chances of success. These systems use a combination of living intuition, rapid calculation and deduction, Dust-enhanced networks, massively parallel search, and political intuition to maximize the outcome of research dollars invested.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT29HarmonyTitle">GALACTIC TRADE CENTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT29HarmonyDescription">Creation of a major financial center on any given planet is a major project -- alien habitats, highly advanced communication infrastructures, specialized universities, and the highest quality shopping and dining are among the pre-requisites. To do this on a level that could turn a solar system into a galactic center of finance is a very rare achievement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT31HarmonyTitle">PERFECT NEGOTIATIONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT31HarmonyDescription">Between observation, study, game theory algorithms, spies, forecasting, and careful consideration of alternatives, almost every negotiation can be resolved in your favor. Highly dependent on the technical capacities of Dust to quantum-compute potential results in real time, few civilizations could imagine achieving this level of domination.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT32HarmonyTitle">AUTOMATED WEALTH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT32HarmonyDescription">With a large enough portfolio of investments and sufficiently advanced systems, it is possible to guarantee a positive return. Based on computing systems powered largely by Dust, investments are likely to be net positive at least until the heat death of the universe. Beyond that point, contract re-negotiation is likely.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT34HarmonyTitle">HARMONIZE PLANETS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT34HarmonyDescription">This powerful ability is only possible for advanced civilizations with high concentrations of population. Caused by harmonic waves that are amplified when the entire surface of a planet is developed by members of the Harmony, it provides powerful boosts to the production of Food, Industry, and Science. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT39AmoebaTitle">XENOSOCIOLOGY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT39AmoebaDescription">A naturally communicative and gregarious species, the Amoebas' society treasures openness and discourse. The science of Groupthink helps encourage the Amoebas to share ideas and common goals with other species as they work toward a peaceful galactic future.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT40AmoebaTitle">EXOTIC RESOURCE LOGISTICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT40AmoebaDescription">It is one thing to pull resources out of the ground; it is quite another to know how to quality check, refine, encapsulate, ship, and receive them. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT41AutomatonTitle">DENSE ORBITALS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT41AutomatonDescription">Though the Automatons are not great explorers, they are efficient users of new technology. In this case, engineers have expanded the Automaton ability to create vast orbital platforms by using technology and techniques from newly discovered species.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT42SwarmTitle">RADIATION HARDINESS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT42SwarmDescription">Developed by Craver biologists, certain treatments applied to developing Craver eggs can result in pupae that are highly resistant to radiation. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT43SwarmTitle">GROUPTHINK</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT43SwarmDescription">While Craver workers and drones were once mindless slaves, the advanced needs of a starfaring nation forced society to give them greater levels of intelligence and autonomy. However, new mass techniques of mind control have been developed to prevent these lower classes from becoming restless.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT45HisshoTitle">WAY OF THE WARRIOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT45HisshoDescription">Though a warlike people, the Hissho have always been insular and clan-based. That is why victory is glorified but expansion into space is not. However, through the application of pedagogy, sociology, propaganda, and subliminals, the good of the greater society could be put ahead of local or clan concerns.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT46HoratioTitle">GALACTIC NUTRITION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT46HoratioDescription">Part of the joy of exploring the galaxy is not just finding new skin care products, but also discovering fascinating new foods. However, given the range and complexity of possible food sources, nutrition science needs to go a long way to determine what is and is not healthy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT47HoratioTitle">DUST COSMETICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT47HoratioDescription">A natural progression in the development of personal beauty treatments, cosmetics that are intelligent and aware have been developed to make sure that no Horatio is ever less than gorgeous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT48ResistanceTitle">HOARDING SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT48ResistanceDescription">As the Pilgrims are a people accustomed to scarcity, they put a great deal of thought into developing systems that preserve goods. In this case, sophisticated energy fields are adapted to extend the natural shelf life of perishable products.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT49EmperorTitle">DUST RETRIEVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT49EmperorDescription">Military and honorable, the Sheredyn are aware that money is one of the ultimate decision makers. Dust retrieval systems were therefore developed to help cull free-floating Dust from areas that they colonize.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT50SophonTitle">DUST STIMULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT50SophonDescription">Only with the most advanced scientific knowledge can one dare to start playing with Dust. The rewards, however, can be great. For instance, by stimulating Dust in a controlled environment, it can be driven to process and problem-solve at tremendous speed. This is a great achievement, if one survives it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT51TerranTitle">WEALTH SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT51TerranDescription">Dust is both a substance and a currency standard; its monetary form can be generated by cutting back on industry and pouring resources into advanced financial operations. However, research can also be done to find those rare instances of self-replicating Dust, which can be fed raw materials to accelerate its activity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT52TerranTitle">INDUSTRIAL HEGEMONY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT52TerranDescription">The growth of the Empire means the growth of its influence. Systems and planets within its frontiers are not merely centers of production; they are agents -- witting or unwitting -- in spreading the cultural, economic, and military influence of the Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT53EmperorTitle">TUNNELED COMMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT53EmperorDescription">Difficulty in controlling vast and complex fleets is always a problem for space navies. By using certain quantum tunneling techniques to communicate instantaneously across great distances, the work of ship and system management can be greatly simplified.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT54EmperorTitle">INVASIVE INFRASTRUCTURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechT54EmperorDescription">This is an unfortunate necessity. In order to pragmatically shuttle materials and troops, entirely new transportation and logistics networks are required. To maximize efficiency, these must run in straight lines and be adjacent to power sources and transport hubs. In other words, they must be built in urban areas, straight through both public and private property.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG01HisshoTitle">ISOTOPE FABRICATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG01HisshoDescription">High-isotope materials are prized for both their material capacities and their energy content. Manufacturing them in large quantities is key to making them economically viable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG22HisshoTitle">POSITRON CONTAINMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG22HisshoDescription">More advanced magnetics permit positrons, a form of anti-matter, to be contained in relatively small units. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG22SwarmTitle">POSITRON CONTAINMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG22SwarmDescription">More advanced magnetics permit positrons, a form of anti-matter, to be contained in relatively small units. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG23EmperorTitle">CONDENSED PLASMA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG23EmperorDescription">With development of more powerful magnetics creating the possibility of harnessing plasma in ever-smaller units, science can create plasma fields -- like a shield system -- around very small units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG25TerranTitle">SEAMLESS CONSTRUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG25TerranDescription">Traditional hull construction required that many plates be joined together. Improved metallurgy, however, now allows the frame of an entire ship to be cast as single, cohesive units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG27HarmonyTitle">PERSONAL SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG27HarmonyDescription">Primarily by bringing energy generation down to a portable size, small vehicles or even augmented individuals can transport their own shield systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG27AutomatonTitle">PERSONAL SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG27AutomatonDescription">Primarily by bringing energy generation down to a portable size, small vehicles or even augmented individuals can transport their own shield systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG27EmperorTitle">PERSONAL SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG27EmperorDescription">Primarily by bringing energy generation down to a portable size, small vehicles or even augmented individuals can transport their own shield systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG38TerranTitle">DARK ENERGY SHIELD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG38TerranDescription">Though its relative invisibility to ancient scientific measures made its true characteristics unknown, in fact dark energy has powerful effects for deflecting and lensing baryonic -- or 'normal' -- matter.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG42SwarmTitle">ANTI-GRAVITON FIELDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG42SwarmDescription">Mastery of nonbaryonic particles and leptons in particular have aided scientists in discovering and manipulating the most elusive force of all -- gravity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG50Title">ADVANCED COUNTERMEASURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG50Description">One step better than surviving a hit is to never be hit at all. Advances in remote sensing, electronics, and particle physics result in improved defensive systems to take out incoming attacks.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG51Title">DUST TO DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG51Description">In order to rapidly evacuate or empty a system, a military technology -- actually a combination of technology and martial procedure -- has been developed that reverts everything to either dust or Dust. Either physical elements are reduced to Dust particles, or the buildings and infrastructures themselves are broken down and sold off.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG51EmperorTitle">DUST TO DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG51EmperorDescription">In order to rapidly evacuate or empty a system, a military technology -- actually a combination of technology and martial procedure -- has been developed that reverts everything to either dust or Dust. Either physical elements are reduced to Dust particles, or the buildings and infrastructures themselves are broken down and sold off.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG51HarmonyTitle">PURIFY PLANETS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG51HarmonyDescription">Delving deeply into the bedrock of a planet, the Harmony installs an infrastructure that nullifies the production of Dust in a system, converting those otherwise wasted resources into Food and Science. Due to the method of construction, the Purifier cannot be scrapped unless the system is Razed or subject to a Bombardment.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG52Title">PLASMA CAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG52Description">Via a single, synchronized high-energy blast of supercharged particles emanating from a number of equally spaced generators, a brief surface of highly destructive plasma can be created in a spherical shape around a building, a ship, or even a planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG53Title">ACTIVE DEFENSES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG53Description">Starships must be immune to many different forces. By developing defensive systems that integrate numerous field types that affect both matter and anti-matter, survivability and longevity increase greatly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG54Title">LOCALIZED STASIS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG54Description">By controlling the decay of particles through the use of local stasis fields, new defensive systems and armors have been created that manipulate all four primary energy sources at once.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG54EmperorTitle">LOCALIZED STASIS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG54EmperorDescription">By controlling the decay of particles through the use of local stasis fields, new defensive systems and armors have been created that manipulate all four primary energy sources at once.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG55HisshoTitle">APPLIED HOLOGRAPHY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG55HisshoDescription">The use of holographic training systems takes a step forward. Recent quantum studies allow real-time communication of certain field and particle types across galactic scales. Hissho scientists have learned to adapt this into holo-comms systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG56HisshoTitle">ENTANGLED PRODUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG56HisshoDescription">At this level of scientific mastery, weapons systems can be fabricated that are quantum-linked, thought-controlled, and partially aware. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG57TerranTitle">SECRET PROJECTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG57TerranDescription">In an advanced and automated empire, it is difficult to obtain money for 'unofficial' projects that do not have a straightforward return on investment calculation. The development of sophisticated and surreptitious systems for finding and distributing funds for these efforts is a complex -- but useful -- exercise.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG58HarmonyTitle">SYSTEMIC UNITY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG58HarmonyDescription">Though the Harmony adapt to the lifestyle of planets and technology, they have not forgotten their past. When a system becomes fully populated, they are able to find resonances within it that let them think and see almost as a single mind.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG59HoratioTitle">GLASSTEEL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG59HoratioDescription">This recently discovered and highly advanced material is transparent, yet has a hardness rating that rivals orichalcix. While the name has nothing to do with its origin or chemical properties, Horatio thought it sounded nice.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG60Title">AUTONOMOUS CONSTRUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG60Description">Infrastructure projects can benefit from this newly developed ability to auto-generate structures. Blueprints, bills of order, storage, planning, fabrication, and construction can now be done rapidly and autonomously by independent machines.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG61Title">BASIC G2A SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG61Description">A number of improvements in mathematics, materials technology, and control systems have come together to perfect the technology required to fire accurately up through the atmosphere to hit objects in orbit.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG62Title">LARGE-SCALE NEURALS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG62Description">While neural networks have existed for ages in theory, models that allow practical application of thinking, real-time interconnected nodes to weapons systems have not been reliably tested until now.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG62HisshoTitle">LARGE-SCALE NEURALS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG62HisshoDescription">While neural networks have existed for ages in theory, models that allow practical application of thinking, real-time interconnected nodes to weapons systems have not been reliably tested until now.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG63HarmonyTitle">METAL MEMORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG63HarmonyDescription">Every particle of matter in the galaxy is unique, when felt through the senses of the Harmony. By developing technology that augments their capacity to sense the signature vibrations of individual atoms, the Harmony can sense the strengths and weaknesses of any construction that contains metals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization1HarmonyTitle">COLONIZATION PROGRAM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization1HarmonyDescription">You can now populate stars far from your starting constellation. However, to do this will require effort at all levels of the society. By creating an official program and stressing the need to sacrifice small comforts in service of a larger cause, some of the discontent caused by colonization can be minimzed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization2HarmonyTitle">ORBITAL COUNSELING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization2HarmonyDescription">Living in the orbitals and bases around gas giants is exceedingly stressful. Lack of privacy, claustrophobia, homesickness, and numerous shortages combine to make life difficult. This counseling program -- a mixture of independent study, individual sessions, psychotherapy, and medication -- greatly reduces stress levels. These principles are then applied to the general population, helping improve the attitudes towards space colonization.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization3HarmonyTitle">VIRTUALIZED COMMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization3HarmonyDescription">Networking and biotech are capable of placing any living being in a largely virtual reality. While the body and its needs cannot be ignored, much of what is play, work, and socialization can be done while tied to a network interface. As the effects of overcrowding, congestion, and noise are suddenly removed from daily life, Approval ratings increase notably.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization4HarmonyTitle">DARK RADIATION TOWERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Overcolonization4HarmonyDescription">Complex anti-matter and dark matter emanations have been shown to potentially have interesting side effects on brainwaves and nervous systems. Dark radiation transmission, on certain frequencies and at certain rhythms, can apparently soothe and calm agitated systems. While it is perhaps not kind or ethical to manipulate populations this way, it is certainly efficient...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus3HarmonyTitle">ALIEN STANDARDS AND SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus3HarmonyDescription">Such a simple thing among members of the same species, and so complex with aliens... trading financial and scientific data requires exhaustive negotiations and complex treaties and explanations covering data formats, measurement standards, time standards, and explanations of exactly what the clause "Act of God" means.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus7HarmonyTitle">ALIEN ESTEEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus7HarmonyDescription">It is a long struggle, but the ability to be seen by multiple alien nations as a reliable and predictable partner reaps innumerable benefits. Whether in diplomacy, trade, or research, the role of a trusted partner is precious and prized.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus8AmoebaTitle">GALACTIC STUDIES CENTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus8AmoebaDescription">This center for higher learning brings together many aliens of many different disciplines with a common goal: To better understand each other and promote trade and discourse throughout the galaxy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus2HarmonyTitle">ALIEN SECURITY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus2HarmonyDescription">A natural next step in opening diplomatic and trade relations is to ensure that traveling members of any species will be welcomed in a way that is healthy and secure for all parties -- from hygiene to cultural preferences to body armor.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1LRTitle">UNSTABLE (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1LRDescription">This version of Unstable Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at long range, where missiles are most effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2LRTitle">PLASMA (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2LRDescription">This version of Plasma Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at long range, where missiles are most effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3LRTitle">POSITRON (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3LRDescription">This version of Positron Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at long range, where missiles are most effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1MRTitle">UNSTABLE (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1MRDescription">This version of Unstable Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at medium range, though missiles are least effective here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2MRTitle">PLASMA (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2MRDescription">This version of Plasma Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at medium range, though missiles are least effective here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3MRTitle">POSITRON (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3MRDescription">This version of Positron Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at medium range, though missiles are least effective here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1SRTitle">UNSTABLE (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1SRDescription">This version of Unstable Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at melee (short) range, where the effect of missiles is average.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2SRTitle">PLASMA (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2SRDescription">This version of Plasma Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at melee (short) range, where the effect of missiles is average.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3SRTitle">POSITRON (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3SRDescription">This version of Positron Missiles is optimized for targeting and effectiveness at melee (short) range, where the effect of missiles is average.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1LRTitle">SYNCHROTRON (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1LRDescription">This version of Synchrotron Lasers is optimized for long range, though Beam weapons are least effective here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2LRTitle">PINCH GUNS (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2LRDescription">These Pinch Guns have been optimized for long range, though Beam weapons are least effective here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3LRTitle">DISRUPTOR (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3LRDescription">This version of Disruptor Beams is optimized to ruin things at long range, though Beam weapons are least effective here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1MRTitle">SYNCHROTRON (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1MRDescription">This version of Synchrotron Lasers is optimized for medium range, where they are most dangerous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2MRTitle">PINCH GUNS (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2MRDescription">These Pinch Guns have been optimized for medium range, where they do most damage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3MRTitle">DISRUPTOR (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3MRDescription">This version of Disruptor Beams is optimized to ruin things at medium range, where they are most effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1SRTitle">SYNCHROTRON (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1SRDescription">This version of Synchrotron Lasers is optimized to target at melee (short) range, where their effectiveness is only average.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2SRTitle">PINCH GUNS (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2SRDescription">These Pinch Guns have been optimized for targeting and effectiveness at melee (short) range, where their effectiveness is only average.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3SRTitle">DISRUPTOR (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3SRDescription">This version of Disruptor Beams is optimized to ruin things at melee (short) range, where their effectiveness is only average.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1LRTitle">HARD KINETICS (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1LRDescription">This version of Hard Kinetics is optimized to put holes in expensive hardware at long range, though at long distances it does the job poorly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2LRTitle">HIGH ISOTOPE (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2LRDescription">These High Isotope Slugs use targeting systems optimized for long range, though at long distances it does the job poorly</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3LRTitle">STRANGE WARHEADS (LONG)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3LRDescription">This version of Strange Warheads disrupts quantum matter from long range, though at long distances it does the job poorly</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1MRTitle">HARD KINETICS (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1MRDescription">This version of Hard Kinetics is optimized to put holes in expensive hardware at medium range, where it is marginally effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2MRTitle">HIGH ISOTOPE (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2MRDescription">These High Isotope Slugs use targeting systems optimized for medium range, where it is marginally effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3MRTitle">STRANGE WARHEADS (MEDIUM)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3MRDescription">This version of Strange Warheads disrupts quantum matter from medium range, where it is marginally effective.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1SRTitle">HARD KINETICS (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1SRDescription">This version of Hard Kinetics is optimized to put holes in expensive hardware at short (melee) range, where it does the most damage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2SRTitle">HIGH ISOTOPE (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2SRDescription">These High Isotope Slugs use targeting systems optimized for short (melee) range, where it does the most damage..</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3SRTitle">STRANGE WARHEADS (MELEE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3SRDescription">This version of Strange Warheads disrupts quantum matter from short (melee) range, where it does the most damage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportArmor6TerranTitle">PLASMA SHIELD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportArmor6TerranDescription">Requiring enormous amounts of energy, this shielding system surrounds the ship with a near-impenetrable barrier of dense, ionized gas.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion1Title">SIEGE KINETICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion1Description">Ship-to-ground projectiles require highly specialized machining as they need to resist heat, friction, and wind.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion2Title">SIEGE ARTILLERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion2Description">As materials science allows ever more powerful charges, payloads, and barrels, ship-based artillery is developed that can fire space-to-surface. As always, key to the success of new warheads is the understanding of the latest defensive armors.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion3Title">SATELLITE BARRIER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion3Description">Part of the work of planetary invasion is to create tight frontiers around targeted systems. A barrier of weaponized satellites, reacting in realtime to numerous data sources, are a very effective way to put additional pressure on planetary populations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion3HisshoTitle">EYES IN THE SKY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion3HisshoDescription">Part of the work of planetary invasion is to create tight frontiers around targeted systems. A barrier of weaponized satellites, reacting in realtime to numerous data sources, are a very effective way to put additional pressure on planetary populations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion4Title">GEOSYNCHRONOUS SNIPER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion4Description">Technology now exists to create space-based kinetic weapons that can accurately hit individual targets as small as two centimeters. For interdiction, assassination, and general mayhem there are few better tools.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion5Title">DROP SHIPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion5Description">Using the technologies created to puncture atmosphere at high velocity through the use of dense, advanced isotopes, a military factory can build landing craft that can safely deliver heavily armed troops in a minimal time window.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion5TerranTitle">PHALANX SHIPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion5TerranDescription">Using the technologies created to puncture atmosphere at high velocity through the use of tightly integrated hulls, a military factory can build landing craft that can safely deliver heavily armed troops in a minimal time window.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion6Title">A-ENTROPIC WEAPONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportInvasion6Description">The last Law of Physics to go is thermodynamics' third, for now armament can be created that locally defies the forces of entropy. These projectiles are capable of piercing a planet and exiting from its far side; excellent for creating fear but rather hard on the geology.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportBomb1Title">CLUSTER MUNITIONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportBomb1Description">These murderous anti-personnel weapons randomly destroy population within a system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportBomb2Title">BUNKER BUSTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportBomb2Description">These bombs, designed for heavy penetration, select and destroy random infrastructure targets in a system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportPower6SwarmTitle">NEUTRINO PULSION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportPower6SwarmDescription">Advanced neutrino capture and decay systems are the ultimate goal for creation of inexpensive and ubiquitous power supplies.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1Title">REALTIME DEFENSES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1Description">A ship's self-protection capabilities can be balanced on-the-fly to react to changing threat profiles. Applying mathematical modeling and game theory, defense systems self-organize to target Fighter and Bomber units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1GenericTitle">BALANCED REALTIME</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1GenericDescription">All of the ship's defensive systems contribute to additional Fighter/Bomber defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1ShieldTitle">SHIELD REALTIME</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1ShieldDescription">The ship's Beam defenses contribute to additional Fighter/Bomber defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1FlakTitle">ANTI-MISSILE REALTIME</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1FlakDescription">The ship's Anti-Missile defenses contribute to additional Fighter/Bomber defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1DeflectorTitle">DEFLECTOR REALTIME</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1DeflectorDescription">The ship's Deflector defenses contribute to additional Fighter/Bomber defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1Title">BOMBER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1Description">These specialized craft are designed to attack enemy ships and participate in star system bombardment. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2Title">HEAVY BOMBER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2Description">Improved shielding means improved survivability. These Heavy Bombers and their plasma payloads are a greater menace to enemy craft.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3Title">REACTIVE BOMBER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3Description">Taking advantage of the latest technologies, reactive systems improve the defensive capabilites of the Bomber while giving its weapons additional armor-piercing punch.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3G2GDescription">Taking advantage of the latest technologies, reactive systems improve the defensive capabilites of the Bomber while giving its weapons additional armor-piercing punch.
 
"We don't call 'em "Leeches" for nothing. Once they target a ship, they won't let go unless you kill 'em." #33CDFF#Sqd. Ldr. Saseav#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4Title">CAUSAL BOMBER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4Description">By using weapons that break down enemy materials at a sub-atomic level, the weapons of these Bombers occasionally cause local interruptions to the nature of causality. So far, permanent changes to known reality have not been observed...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1Title">FIGHTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1Description">Though designed as defensive elements, Fighters not only attack enemy Bombers and ships but can also participate in star system bombardment. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2Title">SHIELDED FIGHTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2Description">Using powerful magnetic fields and high-energy plasma weapons, a new generation of fighters can be built that hit harder and are more durable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3Title">IMPERVIOUS FIGHTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3Description">A requisite in a galaxy with baryonic and non-baryonic weaponry, these fighters are equipped with ultradense hulls and the latest weaponry.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3G2GDescription">A requisite in a galaxy with baryonic and non-baryonic weaponry, these fighters are equipped with ultradense hulls and the latest weaponry.
 
"Without the Elephant's heavy hull, I'd be just another casualty instead of the Hero of the Corana Engagement." #33CDFF#Capt. 'T41' Tifortywun#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4Title">SUPERSTEALTH FIGHTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4Description">Small, powerful, and loaded with technology that approaches magic, these small craft are the pinnacle of engineering. Hard to target due to their advanced hulls and lensing systems, they are the final word in small craft power and durability.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops1Title">ASSAULT TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops1Description">These are highly specialized infantry, trained and equipped to participate in the ground invasion of star systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops2Title">HEAVY TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops2Description">A heavily armed and highly mechanized infantry, these troops are more effective in the invasion of star system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops3Title">ADVANCED MECHS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops3Description">Both troop survivability and firepower are tied to integration of the latest particle weaponry into their mechanized suits. In particular, advanced materials technology is required to isolate troopers from particle effects.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops4Title">AUTOMECH SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroops4Description">The final phase in creating obedient and indestructible ground troops is to remove fallible, slow-to-repair biological systems from them. The most advanced battlefield units are composed of nearly indestructible, highly automated, sentient droids.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize1Title">COORDINATED FLEETS I</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize1Description">A first step in handling large-scale maneuvers and multiple vessels, the use of sensors and systems to coordinate fleet movement provides a tactical advantage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize5Title">COORDINATED FLEETS II</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize5Description">A first step in handling large-scale maneuvers and multiple vessels, the use of sensors and systems to coordinate fleet movement provides a tactical advantage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize6Title">COORDINATED FLEETS III</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize6Description">A first step in handling large-scale maneuvers and multiple vessels, the use of sensors and systems to coordinate fleet movement provides a tactical advantage.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4EmperorTitle">DUST-ENHANCED BARRIERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4EmperorDescription">It is an expensive decision to make, but by adding Dust-driven enhancements to shields and defense systems planetary security can be greatly enhanced.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyTitle">CONTAMINATION BARRIERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyDescription">The effects of Dust on members of the Harmony is devastating. This improvement gives them suits and environments permitting them to take Dust, process it into something useful, and rid the system of its corruption.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementShelter1Title">DAMAGE CONTROL CENTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementShelter1Description">Based on a system-wide infrastructure of tightly coupled sensors, damage -- taken or inflicted -- is tracked, logged, and measured in order to maximize defensive effectiveness as well as aid in post-battle rebuilding.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementShelter2Title">W/P REFLECTORS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementShelter2Description">Specialized alloys are adapted for use as coatings on movable, nano-scale reflectors. Large arrays of these wave/particle reflectors can be used to deflect, reflect, and de-synchronize particle and beam transmissions, whether they are used for communication or weapons. Effects on the enemy can include backfiring or ineffective weapons, communication failure, and great frustration.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementShelter3Title">MASSIVELY PARALLEL COUNTERMEASURES </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementShelter3Description">This project takes counter-measures from a local to a system-wide area of effect. Ground defenses, orbital defenses, and system defenses coordinate the use of energy and resources as well as share data for real-time tracking of all objects foreign to the system. This data is sent instantaneously and allows the most efficient use of firepower; it also leads to efficient recovery and recycling of scrap.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementAntiaircraft1Title">CLOUDRIPPERS (AA)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementAntiaircraft1Description">These ground-to-space defensive guns get their nickname from the powdery trails left behind when they punch up through clouds on the way to their targets.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementAntiaircraft2Title">S2S COUNTERMEASURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementAntiaircraft2Description">Firing from a planetary surface into orbit is a tricky business. By using countermeasures technology in warheads, surface-to-space missiles can avoid perturbances due to atmospheric conditions, debris, and orbital defensive systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementAntiaircraft3Title">STARSTRIKERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementAntiaircraft3Description">A nickname for a highly advanced warhead, these projectiles are covered in a seamless, latticed alloy that is nearly impervious.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1EmperorTitle">XENOTOURISM AGENCIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1EmperorDescription">In order to properly tap into the exploding market of alien tourists, a special infrastructure must be put into place. Travel between planets is a simple problem; travel between cultures is something else indeed. In order to effectively provide an interesting destination for aliens, enormous work is required in public infrastructures, hotels, restaurants, spaceports, and--most particularly--toilets.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAmoeba1Title">APPLIED ASTROFABS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAmoeba1Description">The Amoeba have learned a great deal from their time as a spacefaring race, and this is a concerted effort to apply those lessons to industry and agriculture in aquatic environments. As it turns out, the Amoeba society is capable of great efficiencies when exploiting Ocean worlds.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAutomaton2Title">LIMITED TELEPORTATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAutomaton2Description">In order to maximize their efficiency, the Automatons have harnessed a limited level of teleportation to improve industrial and logistics processes. As the resulting growth in efficiency does not require additional exploration or  travel, it is received very positively.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAutomaton3Title">AUGMENTED STACKING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAutomaton3Description">Primarily through the use of stasis systems and containment fields, additional excess industrial capacity can be stored as parts and Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm1Title">IMPROVED HATCHERIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm1Description">These advanced complexes produce workers that are highly radiation-resistant. As a result, they can be worked harder and longer before they die in the highly irradiated atmosphere of space, which in turn reduces ship maintenance costs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm2Title">HIVE MINDCAST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm2Description">A network of state propaganda transmitters, installed throughout the system, emphasize the glory of the Craver military while transmitting soothing subliminal messages.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm3Title">HIGH-TOLERANCE REACTORS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm3Description">Starship power systems are usually refined, precise miracles of engineering. However, using dirtier fuels obtained from depleted planets, Craver weapon systems have been developed that, while unsafe and dangerous, provide greater power.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony1Title">HARMONIZED TARGETS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony1Description">Using their feel for galactic resources, the Harmony is able to build offensive and defensive systems that 'sense' the nature and style of their opponents. Attack and defense are naturally improved by this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony2Title">CORE CHARTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony2Description">The Harmony is able to design star charts and navigational systems that take advantage of their racial memory as star explorers. Though the ability will fade over time, for a while they will be able to travel more rapidly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony3Title">VIRTUAL DYSON SPHERE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony3Description">As planets move, the thinkers of the Harmony track and control planetary emanations of matter and reality. When a system is fully populated and 'tuned' in this way, Harmony sages can call up an ephemeral Dyson sphere for system defense. Though less effective than the real thing, it is also much less costly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho1Title">C3 SIMULATORS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho1Description">The construction of these advanced particle measuring systems uses quantum coupling to transmit battle information to commanders across the galaxy. As a result, officers and academics can learn in real time.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho2Title">INDOCTRINATION PARKS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho2Description">The creation of these community centers on Hissho planets serves multiple purposes: News, information, and entertainment are presented freely to the populace at the same time that the messages from the emperor are reinforced.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho3Title">MAXIMIZED SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho3Description">By maximizing the useful life and action of every particle in offensive and defensive systems and quantum-coupling them across the galaxy, simple systems are made more effective when fighting several simultaneous battles.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio1Title">FIVE-STAR DRIVE THRU</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio1Description">Why merely eat when you can indulge? There is no better way to speed the healthy and rapid growth of a population than to make the finest imaginable meals available at "fast food" prices.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio2Title">ARID DERMOLOGICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio2Description">For various reasons, Dust-based beauty aids are more effective in dry environments. As these aids are expensive, frivolous, unnecessary, and highly effective, demand for them has gone through the roof -- as have requests to transfer to arid planets.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio3Title">BEAUTIFUL CARGO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio3Description">Ships built with interior glassteel bulkheads allow all Horatios to see what is going on at all times. As even the cargo of these ships is visible, what could be more natural than to load them with the most beautiful thing in the galaxy -- more Horatios?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance1Title">STASIS CENTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance1Description">The Installation of these centers near urban areas provide areas where surplus or donated supplies can be stored. Particularly useful in the event of invasion or blockade, Stasis Centers can supply a populace with goods for many years.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance2Title">ADVANCED TEMPLES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance2Description">These places of worship are more than mere imitations of the Endless or centers of mindless adulation. As Endless wonders are discovered and analyzed, the knowledge hoarded in these temples grows. And as insights grow, so does the admiration of the populace.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance3Title">BARO-AGNOSTIC COMPLEX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance3Description">Though they are religious, the Pilgrims can respect agnosticism if it is well argued. It is more as a joke than for any other reason that they refer to habitats that are unaffected by pressure and gravity as "baro-agnostic."</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueEmperor1Title">BATTLEFIELD PURIFIERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueEmperor1Description">When a victorious battle has ended, Dust is often left behind in the form of actual Dust particles or salvageable goods. This application of Dust retrieval technology allows the Sheredyn to convert the debris of a space battle into currency.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueEmperor2Title">QT C4 MODS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueEmperor2Description">Quantum-tunneled advanced modifications to communication systems appear to be something like magic when first used. These mods help to collect data and command complex systems, offering enormous efficiency gains.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSophon1Title">LOW-IMPACT LABS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSophon1Description">Ecologically designed, virtual, advanced scientific laboratories can be built using nothing more than enormous computer capacity and a willing mind. With few requirements for energy and materials, these can be an extraordinarily efficient way to do research.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSophon2Title">HEARTH DOMES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSophon2Description">What we would call "hearth" translates into Sophon as "place where I can think without being interrupted." By creating habitats and environments reminiscent of traditional Sophon labs and libraries, inhospitable planets can be made appealing for colonization.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSophon3Title">SUPRA-QUANTIC COMPUTING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSophon3Description">Ingredients: Stimulated Dust, solar energy, planet-scale processing complexes of tunneled quantum computers. Directions: Combine, and await results as knowledge advances at a blistering speed. Caution: Remain at 2 light-years distance (minimum).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSower1Title">TASK PATHING PROTOCOLS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSower1Description">A spin-off of Sociologics, Task Pathing is a form of project-oriented programming that aligns Sower priorities. When installed, these protocols tag all decision functions not aligned to a group task as irrelevant, thus guaranteeing cooperation.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSower2Title">CRYO-HYGRO SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSower2Description">Knowledge of cold weather biology and atmospheric conditions has allowed the Sowers to develop this sophisticated terraforming engineering that simplifies transformation into Tundra planets.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran1Title">ADVANCED DUSTGEN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran1Description">Dust can be generated by trade or by fabrication. In this case, enormous containment systems of stimulated Dust can slowly process any physical input into more of this precious substance. The science behind it, for the moment, is not understood, but the results speak for themselves.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran2Title">TRADE BUREAUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran2Description">A key element in projecting the power of the Empire, these governmental offices claim to aid businesses in setting up contacts and deals. In fact, they are efficient centers for transferring information and funds between private, government, and military entities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran3Title">LETHAL TARGETING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran3Description">As science seems to approach magic, some astonishing new technologies have sprung from research focused on a completely different outcome. In this case, weapon damage is incremented via a system that couples particles in real time between weapon and target.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TECHTREE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FollowCamDescription">Click this button to active a tracking mode for the camera which will follow a Fighter squad or a Bomber. 
 
#33CDFF#Left and right arrow keys#REVERT# switch between the Fighters and Bombers. 
#33CDFF#Up and down arrow keys#REVERT# switch between the camera positions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HideHUDTitle">HIDE HUD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HideHUDDescription">Click this button to hide the user interface elements.
 
#33CDFF#'H' key#REVERT# displays the HUD again.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FollowCamDisabledDescription">The follow camera is not available due to the lack of fighters or bombers</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleTechAction1Description">• +40% kinetic efficiency (block: +10%)
• -20% antimissile defense (block: +20%)
• +15% accuracy on  Melee  Weapon (block: +15%)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleTechAction4Description">• +40% evade (block: +10%)
• -20 % damage on Melee Weapon (block: +20%)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleTechAction5Description">• +10% HP repair (block: +10%) [cannot exceed HP at beginning of the fight]
• -10% damage weapons (block: +10%)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleTechAction8Description">• -15% accuracy on opponent (block: -20%)
• +10% accuracy on Long Range Weapon  (block: +10%)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleTechAction10Description">• +20% beam damage (block: +10%)
• +10% accuracy on Medium Range Weapon (block: +10%)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleSelectTargetDescription">Click the action button to select an offensive strategy in the list of your Targeting Options for your major ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NextTargetingAction">PENDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CurrentTargetingAction">CURRENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetTargetingTitle">ORDER - TARGETING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetTargetingCardMainTitle">TARGETING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefaultFleetTargetingTitle">AUTOMATIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefaultFleetTargetingDescription">Default target</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FocusFireFleetTargetingTitle">NOSEBREAKER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FocusFireFleetTargetingDescription">Focus on opponent's 1st ship (depends the formation)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StrongFireFleetTargetingTitle">GUILLOTINE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StrongFireFleetTargetingDescription">1/3 of your fleet targets the three first enemy ships</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpreadFireFleetTargetingTitle">SPREAD FIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpreadFireFleetTargetingDescription">Each one of your ships targets the first enemy ship of the list which is not targeted (or is the least targeted)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HoldFireFleetTargetingTitle">HOLD FIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HoldFireFleetTargetingDescription">No damage done to enemy ships this phase</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetSortingTitle">FORMATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetSortingCardMainTitle">FORMATION </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefaultFleetSortingTitle">DEFAULT FORMATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefaultFleetSortingDescription">Ships with the most HP are at the top of the list</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefensiveFleetSortingTitle">DEFENSIVE FORMATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefensiveFleetSortingDescription">Ships with the highest defense are at the top of the list</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeakerFirstFleetSortingTitle">WEAKER FIRST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeakerFirstFleetSortingDescription">Ships with the least MP are at the top of the list</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StrongestFleetSortingTitle">SHIELD FORMATION </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StrongestFleetSortingDescription">Ships with the most MP are at the top of the list</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MostExperiencedFleetSortingTitle">VETERAN FORMATION </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MostExperiencedFleetSortingDescription">Ships with the most XP are at the top of the list</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ProtectInvadersFleetSortingTitle">PROTECTIVE FORMATION </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ProtectInvadersFleetSortingDescription">Ships with the least invasion MP are at the top of the list</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_BATTLE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyColonizationTitle">VOLCANIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyColonizationDescription">Role: Colonization</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonySmall1Title">METAMORPHIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonySmall1Description">Role: Multiple</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonySmall2Title">TECTONIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonySmall2Description">Role: Multiple</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyMedium1Title">SIMIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyMedium1Description">Role: Multiple</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyMedium2Title">LITHIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyMedium2Description">Role: Multiple</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyLarge1Title">ATHENIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyLarge1Description">Role: Multiple</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyLarge2Title">GRAVITONIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassHarmonyLarge2Description">Role: Multiple</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScoutHarmonyDesign">Scout</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenderHarmonyDesign">Defender</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SuperDefenderHarmonyDesign">Advanced Defender</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AdvancedDefenderHarmonyDesign">Elite Defender</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonyShipHarmonyDesign">Colony</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAmoebaSmall1Title">METHION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAmoebaSmall2Title">ADENON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAmoebaMedium1Title">LYSOS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAmoebaMedium2Title">BACTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAmoebaLarge1Title">PROTEUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAmoebaLarge2Title">PROTEUS B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAutomatonSmall1Title">CUTTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAutomatonSmall2Title">CULLER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAutomatonMedium1Title">SICKLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAutomatonMedium2Title">THRESHER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAutomatonLarge1Title">HARVESTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassAutomatonLarge1Title">HARVESTER B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassEmperorSmall1Title">CORVETTE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassEmperorSmall2Title">DESTROYER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassEmperorMedium1Title">CRUISER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassEmperorMedium2Title">BATTLESHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassEmperorLarge1Title">DREADNOUGHT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassEmperorLarge2Title">DREADNOUGHT B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHarmonySmall1Title">METAMORPHIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHarmonySmall2Title">TECTONIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHarmonyMedium1Title">SIMIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHarmonyMedium2Title">LITHIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHarmonyLarge1Title">ATHENIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHarmonyLarge2Title">GRAVITONIC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHisshoSmall1Title">HAWK</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHisshoSmall2Title">FALCON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHisshoMedium1Title">PHOENIX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHisshoMedium2Title">CONDOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHisshoLarge1Title">ROC</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHisshoLarge2Title">ROC B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHoratioSmall1Title">BARO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHoratioSmall2Title">COMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHoratioMedium1Title">DUX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHoratioMedium2Title">ARCHIDUX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHoratioLarge1Title">IMPERATOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassHoratioLarge2Title">IMPERATOR B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassResistanceSmall1Title">DISCIPLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassResistanceSmall2Title">VINDICATOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassResistanceMedium1Title">RELIANT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassResistanceMedium2Title">VALIANT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassResistanceLarge1Title">PALADIN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassResistanceLarge2Title">ORACLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSophonSmall1Title">DEKA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSophonSmall2Title">KILO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSophonMedium1Title">GIGA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSophonMedium2Title">PETA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSophonLarge1Title">YOTTA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSophonLarge2Title">YOTTA B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSowerSmall1Title">SURVEYOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSowerSmall2Title">HAMMER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSowerMedium1Title">AXE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSowerMedium2Title">ANVIL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSowerLarge1Title">PILEDRIVER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSowerLarge2Title">PILEDRIVER B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSwarmSmall1Title">RAIDER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSwarmSmall2Title">MARAUDER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSwarmMedium1Title">PREDATOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSwarmMedium2Title">REAPER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSwarmLarge1Title">ANNIHILATOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassSwarmLarge2Title">ANNIHILATOR B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassTerranSmall1Title">CORVETTE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassTerranSmall2Title">DESTROYER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassTerranMedium1Title">CRUISER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassTerranMedium2Title">BATTLESHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassTerranLarge1Title">DREADNOUGHT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassTerranLarge2Title">DREADNOUGHT B</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_SHIP" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_FLEET" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero74LastName">Dar-Omnis</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero74FirstName1">Mani</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero74Description">Though a member of a society known for industrial efficiency, Dar-Omnis’s interests lay in the psychology and motivation of sentient beings – whether animated by blood or circuitry. This Automaton studied social structures and networks in order to discover the secrets of leadership, motivation, and the development of sentient relations. Studying Dust networks in the lab one day in search of greater understanding of resilient interactions, Dar-Omnis was exposed to a high concentration of dispersed Dust. Now its advanced emotional intelligence is combined with an ability to make faultless decisions, making it an extremely efficient leader.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero74FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero75LastName">Lucrum</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero75FirstName1">Yoku</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero75Description">The name Lucrum is well known among traders, bankers, and grumpy casino owners across the galaxy. A genius at probability and statistics, Lucrum was in the middle of playing five simultaneous hands of high-speed Sophon blackjack with a six-deck pack when he was struck by a moment of lucidity. In a brief flash he realized that his long-term exposure to Dust had given him supra-genius mental capacity, that he would have an incredible future with the mysterious and covert guild known as the Dust Collective, and that the strange, secretive woman who he seemed to keep running into was actually their recruiting agent, waiting for him to realize what was going on. Now a key figure in the Collective, Lucrum understands the fine boundary where risk meets reward perhaps better than any other living being. This fact masks another, more interesting skill: An excellent comprehension of the practical powers and limits of Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero75FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero76LastName">Ponders</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero76FirstName1">CUSO4 </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero76Description">Unlike many elements of the Harmony, who were completely disoriented by their contact with Dust, this one was intrigued rather than confused by the sudden onslaught of individuality and the need to generate productive work. A thinker and philosopher, it was eager to try out bizarre social constructs like having a ‘name’ and doing a ‘job’. Now a scientist specializing in waves and particles, Ponders uses its instinctive and inductive thought process to feel the movement of galactic bodies and sense the shape of galactic matter.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero76FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero77LastName">8043</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero77FirstName1">Enil-Nex</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero77Description">An escaped viral lab experiment that evolved into a useful member of galactic society, Enil-Nex’s rise to sentience moderated its drive to control and consume into a simple desire to survive. Learning that through cooperation it could gain more than through conflict, Enil-Nex understood that its defensive skills as a viral entity (mutating forms, reacting to pathogens, building up resistances, allocating resources) translated surprisingly well when using Dust, rather than biological life, as a vector for its actions. Now a Hero skilled in planetary defense, it is well-liked and -respected (though rarely hugged).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero77FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero79LastName">Zolya</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero79FirstName1">Tulela</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero79Description">"A true Zolya." Tulela had first heard that phrase used in reference to her during a planetary hunting expedition at age ten, when she had used her mother's rifle to kill a sabertooth that was prowling around the carcasses they had skinned and hung. Another in that famous dynasty of orange-haired, fearless adventurers, Tulela rose to leadership of her clan at twenty-six and successfully marshaled the survivors when the pirates of the ABC burned them out of their haven. Seeking another home, she took the decision to restore her family to Auriga when her family's combat medic and problem solver, Opbot, figured out its probable galactic coordinates. Independent, canny, and fearless, it is said that Tulela has far more friends than enemies -- because the enemies don't survive very long.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero79FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero80LastName">D0t3H01</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero80FirstName1">Opbot</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero80Description">Opbot has been working for Zolya's clans ever since they rescued him from the slow destruction of the planet Auriga. A highly efficient medical robot, Opbot's skills in surgery, first aid, and emergency medicine were frequently required by the Zolya family's tumultuous  lifestyle. He never forgot the ruins of Auriga, however, and one day after centuries of service Opbot decided to rediscover the lost planet. That work required many decades, however, due to the fact that living with the Zolya included a lot of fighting, running, attacking, escaping, blowing up ships, and getting one's own ship blown up. When he finally came down to a five-sigma probability of Auriga's location, he presented his findings to Tulela Zolya. Though at first indifferent, Opbot was able to convince her that something of value -- in fact, of enormous value -- was still hidden there.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero80FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_HERO" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombPopulationTitle">AP BOMBS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombPopulationDescription">These murderous anti-personnel weapons randomly destroy population within a system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombImprovementTitle">BOMBS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombImprovementDescription">These bombs, designed for heavy penetration, select and destroy random infrastructure targets in a system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleTitle">SPECIAL MODULES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleBomberTitle">BOMBERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleBomberDescription">Bombers that attack enemy ships and participate in star system bombardment. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleFighterTitle">FIGHTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleFighterDescription">Fighters to attack enemy Bombers, ships and participate in star system bombardment. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleTroopsTitle">TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleTroopsDescription">Landing troops that participate in the invasion of a star system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModulePointDefenseTitle">POINT DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModulePointDefenseDescription">Point defense technology uses existing defensive systems (armor, shields, flak) to augment a ship's capability to destroy Fighters and Bombers.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleValueFormat">$EffectiveCount/$Count</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleCategoryInvasionDescription">Modules that enhance the ship invasion capabilities</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleUnitResourcesPrerequisitesDescription">A strategic resource is needed for this module (mouse over the module icon for more details).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignModuleAddDescription">Click to add a copy of this module to your ship design.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignModuleMissingReqDescription">Cannot add a copy of this module: missing requirements.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignModuleSubtractDescription">Click to remove one copy of this module to your ship design.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipDesignModuleNoneDescription">Cannot remove a copy of this module: no module left.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExceededCapacityModuleSpecializationDescription">The quantity of special modules you have equipped exceeds the capacity of this ship design.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UnlockedSlotModuleSpecializationDescription">The hull of this ship design has a slot available for specialization.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LockedSlotModuleSpecializationDescription">The hull of this ship design does not have this specialization slot.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleInvasionTitle">SIEGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleInvasionDescription">Modules that speed up the siege of a star system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroopsSpecialization1Title">TROOPERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroopsSpecialization2Title">ELITE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialTroopsSpecialization3Title">NUMEROUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighterSpecialization1Title">BALANCED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighterSpecialization2Title">BATTLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighterSpecialization3Title">INVASION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomberSpecialization1Title">BALANCED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomberSpecialization2Title">BATTLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomberSpecialization3Title">INVASION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefenseSpecialization1Title">DEFLECTOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefenseSpecialization2Title">SHIELD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefenseSpecialization3Title">ANTI-MISSILE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LongRangeShortTitle">(LR)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MediumRangeShortTitle">(MR)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShortRangeShortTitle">(M)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LongRangeTitle">LONG RANGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MediumRangeTitle">MEDIUM RANGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShortRangeTitle">MELEE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RangeClassDescription">Click to change the effective range of your modules.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ArchetypeDescription">Click to change the archetype of your modules.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecializationDescription">Click to change the specialization of your modules.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSelectLevelUpDescription">Click to view the superior level of the module.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSelectLevelDownDescription">Click to view the inferior level of the module.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleCancelChangeDescription">Click to cancel the changes.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleApplyChangeDescription">Click to apply this module level and/or the other changes.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSelectLevelUpDisabledDescription">There is no superior module available. Note that some modules have only 1 level though (civilian, bombs).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSelectLevelDownDisabledDescription">There is no inferior module.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MODULE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCeaseFireTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Unreasonable, this is? We believe that reaching out in a spirit of synchronism improves a conflictual situation.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCeaseFireTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Judicious, this seems. A cease fire is certainly preferable to continuing our mutual conflict. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCeaseFireTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Enticing, is it not, our idea? We imagine trading messages to be an improvement on trading salvos.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Irrational these thoughts may be. Yet we persist in seeking co-operative solutions to worsening relationships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Provocative, is it not? Further cooperation can but enhance out mutual goals and the greater equilibrium.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Compelling, our gambit must be! As we admire your people, the thought of closer cooperation presents itself.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Ludicrous this may appear. But we feel that by proposing this alliance we can forestall the worst.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Tantalizing, our scenario: Deeper cooperation, greater concordance, lesser conflict. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Beguiling is our offer! We are persuaded that deepening our natural associations will bring enormous serendipity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingDeclareWarTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Inconceivable! That is our opinion. However, when options are reduced to one, we bow to and embrace the inevitable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingDeclareWarTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Prudent, we feel this is. If we continue to ignore our obvious antipathy, it would disserve our greater ambitions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingDeclareWarTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Outrageous, we agree! Yet we feel no other alternative manifests itself in spite of our esteem.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Eccentric, you may think we are. Yet in our experience, mutual reliance offers greater long-term prosperity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Discerning, we are. Growing an alliance between our societies inevitably cultivates the greater good.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Enthralling - that is how we find your culture. We can only imagine an alliance transformed by your august presence.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingLeaveAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Insulting - is that your reaction? Regardless, in our estimation departure from the alliance is the wisest course.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingLeaveAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Perspicacious, this proposal seems. We are convinced that the alliance can be further improved by your absence.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingLeaveAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Intriguing, we feel, not surprising. Your greater aspirations may be better served outside the constraints of our alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingPeaceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Unthinkable, really? We extend this proposal in spite of that, submitting that peace is preferable to conflict.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingPeaceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Interesting, at the least. We hope to ease discordance, improve affiliations, and encourage propinquity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingPeaceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Fascinating you are! Perhaps through peace more wondrous phenomena might occur than could do so through war.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOpenBordersTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Ridiculous? Perhaps. Yet a gesture of trust could well remedy our deteriorating relations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOpenBordersTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Inviting, this recommendation is! We act in a spirit of greater concord, seeking meaningful discourse between our peoples.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOpenBordersTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Captivating, this appears to us. We are convinced that greater mutual comprehension will improve our individual goals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOtherTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Facetious you may find our proposal. Yet our worsening affairs compel us to seek mercantile solutions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOtherTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Thoughtful, we are. We hope to match the equilibrium of our relations with measured, sagacious commerce.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOtherTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Stimulating, to say the least. Let us see if greater economic intimacy brings even better conceptual concordance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermHarmonyLeft">Ridiculous, approaching madness. We do not entirely understand why you offer this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermHarmonyMidLeft">Unlikely, given the data. Though we understand you are making an effort.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermHarmonyMidRight">Interesting, your desire for peace. We consider that your proposal arrives propitiously.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermHarmonyRight">Entrancing, this notion. What could we desire more than an end to conflict and improved communication?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyLeft">Foolish, to say the least. We are curious as to why you feel this to be of interest.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyMidLeft">Doubtful, as it stands currently. But we appreciate that you are willing to discuss.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyMidRight">Appealing, it is. We believe that improved cooperation brings greater equilibrium.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermHarmonyRight">Excellent, your thinking. It is our belief that mutual cooperation leads to mutual profit. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyLeft">Insipid, in our opinion. We do not see sense in your alliance -- or your proposal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyMidLeft">Dubious, this idea. Though there may be promise, acceptance of the current proposal would be injudicious.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyMidRight">Titillating, we might say! We dream of alliances that build harmoniously toward a prosperous future.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermHarmonyRight">Excellent, unquestionably!  We predict a glorious future for the associated communities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Unsurprising, obviously. Our relations were trending in this direction.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Unnecessary, we feel. But such a declaration hardly requires our agreement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Melancholy is our mood! How sad that as relations seemed to be improving, you choose to destroy them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyLeft">"Ludicrous" is an appropriate term. How could we associate with beings who so poorly understand us?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyMidLeft">Improbable, in our estimation. Not impossible, but unlikely given current parameters.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyMidRight">Tantalizing, we do agree. Our destiny is to conjoin efforts and render the galaxy more equanimous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermHarmonyRight">Irresistible, your proposal! Together our empires shall build a numinous destiny.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendWorsening">Heartbreaking, though inevitable, given the unfortunate state of our relations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendStable">Unfortunate, even precipitate! Is departure from our community the sole possibility?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermHarmonyAttitudeTrendImproving">Reckless, undoubtedly! Your inauspicious decision renders us disconsolate.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermHarmonyLeft">Doomed to failure. We cannot understand that such an important subject is broached so churlishly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermHarmonyMidLeft">Implausible, your prospectus. We are inclined towards peace, but wary of precipitous action.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermHarmonyMidRight">Alluring are the words of your diplomats. A sane and sagacious people can only wish for peace.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermHarmonyRight">Enthralling, this treaty you proffer! great civilizations advance through harmonious concordance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermHarmonyLeft">Impossible, of course. We cannot comprehend an act if such sincerity after an offer of such insincerity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermHarmonyMidLeft">Suspicious, as we see it. Your offer is neither absurd, nor completely unobjectionable. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermHarmonyMidRight">Seductive, even desirable. We see opportunities for greater sympathy and sincerity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermHarmonyRight">Fascinating, this prospectus. We are persuaded that such generous terms indicate great opportunities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermHarmonyLeft">Risible, at best. We are not convinced that you understand the concept of "fair trade."</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermHarmonyMidLeft">Unconvincing, this gambit. We are not opposed a priori, but find this insufficiently felicitous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermHarmonyMidRight">Attractive, your offer! We hold the hope that our nations achieve greater co-prosperity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermHarmonyRight">Bewitching this offer is. How could reasonable sentients, as we strive to be, respond negatively?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermMilitaryPowerTense">Your military buildup has triggered a military response from the $Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermMilitaryPowerWeaknessStress">Your weakness makes you look like an easy target for the $Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermScoreTense">Your increasingly high score has made the $Empire view you as a threat.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermLivingSpaceTense">The $Empire are running out of space for their population.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermOwningLegitimateTerritory">The $Empire wish to reclaim the systems that were previously theirs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermBrokenExchange">You broke the terms of a treaty with the $Empire; this has triggered hostilities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermAnotherAlliance">You have joined another Alliance, and the $Empire respond to treachery with war.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermConnectionSpaceTense">The $Empire wish to ease the border tensions between your empires.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermPeaceful">The $Empire note your peaceful relations and propose a treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermCommonEnemyOrFriends">Your empire and the $Empire have similar relations with other nations, so the $Empire propose a treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermMilitaryPowerRespect">Your military strength has impressed the $Empire, who propose a treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermMilitaryPowerPity">The $Empire take pity on your weakness, and propose a treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermSecuringNeighbourhood">Your efforts to secure the region are appreciated by the $Empire, who offer a treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermSecuringNeighbourhood">The $Empire offer Open Borders in appreciation for your stabilizing the region.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermMilitaryPowerPity">The $Empire offer an Open Borders treaty out of pity for your military weakness.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermMilitaryPowerRespect">The $Empire note your relative military power, and propose Open Borders out of respect.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermConnectionSpaceTense">To calm tempers on your shared frontier, the $Empire propose Open Borders with you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermCurrentExchangesOrPastExchange">The $Empire appreciate your history of commercial exchange and propose Open Borders.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermDonations">Your generosity towards the $Empire has resulted in their offer of an Open Borders treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementTermAlliance">As a member of the same Alliance, the $Empire offer a Cooperation Agreement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementTermCurrentExchangesOrPastExchange">Based on good commercial relations, the $Empire offer a Cooperation Agreement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementTermCommonEnemy">You and the $Empire have a common enemy; they propose a Cooperation Agreement for mutual support.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementTermDonations">The $Empire thank you for your generosity, and suggest a Cooperation Agreement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementTermMilitaryPowerPity">The $Empire propose a Cooperation Agreement, taking pity on your military weakness.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermOpenBorderOrCooperationAgreement">The $Empire propose an Alliance, given your excellent diplomatic relations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermCurrentExchangesOrPastExchange">Your good commercial relations compel the $Empire to propose an Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermSecuringNeighbourhood">The $Empire note you have helped stabilized the region and propose an Alliance for this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermMilitaryPowerRespect">Your great military power is respected by the $Empire, who propose an Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermMilitaryPowerPity">The $Empire note your weak military, and propose an Alliance for your defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermCommonEnemyOrFriends">Noting your similar diplomatic relations, the $Empire propose to form an Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermCurrentExchangesOrPastExchange">Based on a history of good commercial relations, the $Empire invite you to join their Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermOpenBorderOrCooperationAgreement">You have very good diplomatic relations with the $Empire, who invite you into their Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermSecuringNeighbourhood">You have helped stabilize this corner of the galaxy, so the $Empire invite you into their Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermMilitaryPowerRespect">The $Empire see your great military strength, and would like to have that in their Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermMilitaryPowerPity">The Alliance with the $Empire as a member sees you are weak, so the $Empire ask you to join them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermCommonEnemyOrFriends">As you have common friends and enemies, the $Empire invite you to enter their Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_DIPLOMACY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsGameIntroductionTitle_AddOn7">Chronicles of the Lost</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsGameIntroductionDescription_AddOn7">The galaxy is vast, and its secrets too many to count. Given the many civilizations that have risen and fallen since the advent of intelligent life, it is certain that great knowledge, vast riches, and gruesome tales all await the hand of the intrepid voyager 
As space is further explored and more systems become homes for new colonists, bit by bit the secrets of the old peoples will see the light of day. What more is there to learn of the Endless and their allies and enemies? Only time, and Dust, and tenacity will bring the answer...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsGameIntroductionTitle">The Search For Auriga</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsGameIntroductionDescription">Generations ago, Nadjne Zolya made room for Opbot in an overcrowded ship leaving a dying planet. Though Opbot was a skilled medical operative, he had accepted that the humanoids would save themselves first and leave him to decay as magneto-gravitational cataclysms made the planet of Auriga unlivable. Surprised by their offer, Opbot repayed the Zolya clan for decades, then centuries, as their restless, homeless clans moved from planet to planet, system to system, and battle to battle.

Driven from their simple tundra world by a fleet of pirates, they once again took up the life of homeless marauders. It was then that Opbot had the idea to rediscover Auriga; an idea that quickly blossomed in to an all-consuming passion. But memories are faulty, galaxies move, and records are often missing or poorly kept; it turned out to be far more complex than he thought.
 
It was hundreds of years later that he was sure enough of his findings to present them to a very hesitant Tulela. But Opbot told her of what he remembered: Endless warrens of laboratories, storehouses of knowledge, ruins and artifacts scattered across the landscape like pebbles on a beach. In the end, Tulela agreed to seek that lost and fabled planet.

As their tiny fleet arrives, other civilizations that have tracked them or searched themselves for the planet begin to appear; the name of Auriga is famed across the settled galaxy. Auriga will once again become a focus of war and strife, for whatever faction can find, and hold, this precious world will have access to the greatest scientific wisdom of the galaxy.
</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsGameIntroductionTitle_Xpack">DISHARMONY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsGameIntroductionDescription_Xpack">The Harmony has arrived. Not like a meteor shower or a landslide, but like erosion or plate tectonics. They have been moving since the birth of the universe, passing through the galaxies, as they seek The Core. Their migration was deliberate, calm, inevitable.
Dust was their downfall. In the galaxy of the Endless they were ensnared; this strange technological creation that affected particles, fields and waves broke the single movement of the Harmony into a cacaphony of individual elements. The Dust took away their propulsion, their ability to hear the resonances of the universe, and their shared consciousness; in their place it offered language, individuality, mechanics, and control. Their brethren continue elsewhere in the universe, unknowing and unaffected. But in this galaxy, the Harmony have fallen from grace and turned into gravity-enchained individuals.
 
The Harmony saw Dust, then, as an infecting menace or a plague. With their new-found skills of ship construction they began to take measures to destroy it -- measures that they saw as necessary and entirely moral. What the Harmony would refer to as the Righteous Cleansing will be referred to by others as the Harmony Wars, for the Harmony made no differentiation between "inhabited" and "uninhabited". To them, a planet could only be categorized as either "infected" or "clean." 
 
Attacking in small, individual ships that are difficult to hit, purposefully targeting Dust-infected infrastructures and populations, the rest of the galaxy lived the arrival of the Harmony as a minor apocalypse. Other peoples will respond in kind, creating Fighter and Bomber craft to counter the Harmony's unusual tactics, bringing the war to their enemy. Planetary bombardment and invasion will take a new turn; new heroes will rise up to counter the threats.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportShipsLostFormatSingle">#33CDFF#$Number#REVERT# SHIP LOST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportShipsLostFormatPlural">#33CDFF#$Number#REVERT# SHIPS LOST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportShipsDestroyedFormatSingle">#33CDFF#$Number#REVERT# ENEMY SHIP DESTROYED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportShipsDestroyedFormatPlural">#33CDFF#$Number#REVERT# ENEMY SHIPS DESTROYED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportHeroXPGain">$First $Last HAS GAINED $Number XP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportHeroInjured">$First $Last HAS BEEN INJURED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportOffenseTotalDamage">EFFECTIVE DAMAGES: #33CDFF#$Number#REVERT# Ḩ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportWeaponsAverageEfficiencyFormat">AVERAGE WEAPONS' EFFICIENCY: #33CDFF#$Number%#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportBestWeaponFormat">BEST WEAPON: #33CDFF#$Class#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportWeaponsAverageEfficiencyNoWeapon">AVERAGE WEAPONS' EFFICIENCY: #33CDFF#-#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportNoBestWeapon">BEST WEAPON: #33CDFF#-#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportDefensesAverageEfficiencyFormat">AVERAGE DEFENSES' EFFICIENCY: #33CDFF#$Number%#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportBestDefenseFormat">BEST DEFENSE: #33CDFF#$Class#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportDefensesAverageEfficiencyNoDefense">AVERAGE DEFENSES' EFFICIENCY: #33CDFF#-#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportNoBestDefense">BEST DEFENSE: #33CDFF#-#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventEncounterFleetFormationTitle">FLEET FORMATION &amp; TARGETING TO PLAY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventEncounterFleetTargetingTitle">FLEET TARGETING TO PLAY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModuleBomberTitle">BOMBERS' WEAPONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModuleFighterTitle">FIGHTERS' WEAPONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleBomberTitle">EVADE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleFighterTitle">EVADE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventSystemRecycledTitle">Plundering $System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventSystemRecycledDescription">$System has been pillaged for $Dust</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarningSystemRecycledTooltipTitle">PLUNDERING REPORT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventSystemRazedTitle">Razing $System </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventSystemRazedDescription">$System has been razed</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventFocusDescription">Click to minimize the panel and focus the camera on the system where the event occurs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarningSystemRazedTooltipTitle">RAZING REPORT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Achievement_SpeedBonusHarmonyTitle">CORE CHARTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Achievement_SpeedBonusHarmonyDescription">The Harmony is able to design star charts and navigational systems that take advantage of their racial memory as star explorers. Though the ability will fade over time, for a while they will be able to travel more rapidly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASattitudeincreasedFormat">You notice that your relationship with $Empire has improved.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASattitudedecreasedFormat">You notice that your relationship with $Empire has degraded.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASGalaxySaturationTitle">$Empire is reacting to the population density of the galaxy and the speed with which colonial expansion is occurring.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASNeedOfNewIncomeTitle">$Empire seems to be unable to accumulate Dust, and needs to find additional sources of revenue.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASMilitaryBalanceTitle">$Empire is noting -- very carefully -- the current balance of power and the impact of your military strength. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASMilitaryPowerScoreTitle">The power of your fleets is of great interest to $Empire. Strength and weakness can both affect diplomatic standing.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASAttitudeTitle">In the great game of diplomacy enemies can become friends, and vice versa. $Empire is beginning to look at you in a different light.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASRankMotivationTitle">The relative rank of your nation among the peoples of the galaxy is currently preoccupying the political discussions of $Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASNeedAllianceAgentTitle">Certain other peoples in the galaxy, in particular $Empire, think that it may be wise for you to rethink your strategy of alliances.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASAllowWarAgentTitle">Exploration of the galaxy is well under way, and it is time to change the diplomatic stakes. $Empire even wonders if the time for military conflict has arrived...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASWarFatigueTitle">$Empire cannot help but note the unusual duration of the current war. Is perseverance an advantage or a flaw?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASMilitarySituationTitle">In any protracted conflict there will be winners and losers. $Empire has noticed which side you have ended up on.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASOutpostRatioTitle">Your rate of expansion, and the number of Outposts versus the number of established colonies, is the subject of discussions among $Empire diplomats. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASTradeRouteIncomeTitle">Commerce is vital to the development of the galaxy, and $Empire is noting the revenue that your trade routes generate.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASVictoryCompletionForFirstEmpireTitle">It can be risky to be seen as too powerful, for then other foes may group together in opposition. $Empire is wondering if the time is ripe to oppose the leading empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASScoreTitle">The political analysts of $Empire have ranked the empires of the galaxy according to their level of success. Your position in that ranking is attracting attention.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AMASNeedExplorationTitle">The galaxy can be explored widely or understood deeply; $Empire believes that the balance between those two objectives is not ideal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventRallyPointNoPathTitle">RALLY POINT UNREACHABLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventRallyPointNoPathDescription">Fleet $Fleet cannot reach its rally point. The fleet will stay in orbit awaiting for your orders to move. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarningRallyPointNoPathTooltipTitle">RALLY POINT UNREACHABLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemVisitedTitle">Auriga System Discovered!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemVisitedDescription">The star around which the legendary planet Auriga orbits has been discovered!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemColonizedTitle">Auriga System Colonized</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemColonizedDescription">The system that holds the famous planet Auriga has been colonized!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnColonizedTitle">Planet Auriga Colonized!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnColonizedDescription">Daring adventurers have settled Auriga, the lifeless planet rich in ruins and history.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnMoonExploredTitle">Auriga Moon Surveyed</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnMoonExploredDescription">On the moon Noren that orbits Auriga, a temple of the Endless has been surveyed</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnWonderRestoredTitle">Auriga Rises!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnWonderRestoredDescription">The ancient Wonder that crowned the planet Auriga has been restored, and the faction that holds the system now gains its powers.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnTerraformedTitle">Auriga Altered</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnTerraformedDescription">Terraforming has been executed on the planet Auriga, changing its very nature but not the secrets that it holds.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemConqueredTitle">Auriga Falls!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemConqueredDescription">The Auriga system has been conquered by another faction; another people now hold this legendary world.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemRazedTitle">Planet Auriga Razed</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemRazedDescription">The installations and infrastructure of the planet Auriga have been razed, yet the secrets of its past remain.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnDepletedTitle">Planet Auriga Depleted</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnDepletedDescription">Colonized by a greedy faction, the planet Auriga has been depleted of its resources and its once-rich surface is now an over-exploited wasteland.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemPurifiedTitle">Auriga System Purified</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NarrativeEventsAurigaOnSystemPurifiedDescription">The energies of Dust have been siphoned off Auriga, removing some of the strangeness from this famous planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DisplayRallyPointsTitle">Display Rally Points</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DisplayRallyPointsDescription">Toggle this to display the locations of Rally Points.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventRallyPointInvalidTitle">Rally Point Failure</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EventRallyPointInvalidDescription">Due to a change in the galactic diplomatic situation, one or more of your Rally Points is no longer usable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarningRallyPointInvalidTooltipTitle">Rally Point no longer usable</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventTitle">COLONIZATION EVENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventFormat">COLONIZATION EVENT: #33CDFF#$PlanetName#REVERT# </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventSummaryTitle">COLONIZATION EVENT SUMMARY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExternalColonizationEventSummaryTitle">EXTERNAL COLONIZATION EVENT SUMMARY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectDescriptorOnSystemFormat">$System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectDescriptorOnPlanetFormat">$Planet</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_01Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_01Description">Exploration has its hazards and its rewards. This system is almost like a gift waiting to be unwrapped; remnants of orbital stations from an ancient civilization await your scientists. They are curious, as the ruins do not seem to be from the Endless.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_02Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_02Description">Your exploration vessel has arrived safely in a new system. You find an old probe of unknown design that contains a map of much of the surrounding regions of space.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_03Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_03Description">The nation is excited at the discovery of a new planetary system. Your explorers are perplexed, however, as there is a high concentration of Dust yet no trace of the Endless.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_04Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_04Description">Another alien system, complete with more alien ruins. One cannot but wonder how many peoples rose, flourished, and fell in the silence of the galaxy; many peoples other than the Endless left their traces.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_05Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_05Description">This system contains remnants of enormous, ancient ruins, with deposits of Dust in strange shapes and forms. For the first time, even the mountains were sculpted into decorations for some ancient race of vastly wealthy - and powerful - beings.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06Description">This system contained an ancient foundry that apparently created copies of ships for some long-lost race. You gain an additional vessel, but the factory consumes itself to provide the materials. The traces that remain do not resemble in the least the technology of the Endless.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06_1Title">HOSTILE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06_1Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06_2Title">SELFISH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06_2Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06_3Title">HELPFUL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_06_3Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07Description">It seems that you are not the first sentient beings on the planet, though judging by the remains the previous inhabitants died warring, using vast weapons of Dust in the air and on the ground.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07_1Title">HOSTILE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07_1Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07_2Title">SELFISH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07_2Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07_3Title">HELPFUL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_07_3Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_08Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Reward_Exploration_08Description">The vegetation of this planet is different from the one the settlers knew. Brown and purple are as present as green, with strange plants aligned in vast fields and orchards by ancient and long-lost hands.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_01Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_01Description">Exploration has its hazards and its rewards. Here, at least, a ship touches down safely and a new life begins - though the act of colonization is often far less simple.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_02Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_02Description">Your crew has had a safe landing and much of the equipment survived the voyage -- congratulations on a successful colonization. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_03Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_03Description">The nation breathes a sigh of relief at another successful colonization. So much can go wrong, between technology and psychology, that any success is a great success.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_04Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_04Description">Another alien planet, and additional alien ruins. One cannot but wonder how many peoples rose, flourished, and fell in the silence of the galaxy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_05Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_05Description">Remains of ruins, of Dust, of strange shapes and forms. In this strange place, seems that the mountains were even sculpted like decorations for the wealthy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_06Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_06Description">The planet appears empty of traces of ancient civilizations; sometimes ruins and artifacts are even stranger when they are absent.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07Description">It seems that you are not the first sentient beings on the planet, though judging by the remains the previous inhabitants died warring, knee-deep their own pollution.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07_1Title">HOSTILE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07_1Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07_2Title">SELFISH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07_2Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07_3Title">HELPFUL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_07_3Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_08Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventStandard_08Description">The vegetation of this planet is different from the one the settlers knew. Brown and purple are as present as green, and the children in particular are frightened by the shapes of the trees.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_01Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_01Description">The more you see of the universe, the more you realize you know nothing. Here, for instance, you have found ancient ruins, and ponder their meaning. Outpost? Monastery? Expedition?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_02Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_02Description">As you explore, you find ruins full of Dust tracery. You believe that they were left by the Endless, the first colonizers of this vast galaxy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_03Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_03Description">Another planet yields its mysteries! And yet, adds new ones. For though there are ruins that you believe were by the Endless, there are other, older ruins beneath them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_04Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_04Description">The remains on this planet were of an ancient civilization. Most likely the Endless, though with all of the different sects and migrations even some of the Endless do not resemble the Endless.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_05Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_05Description">With new colonization, knowledge of archaeology progresses. You even discover ruins that do not seem to belong to the Endless, but to other lost peoples.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06Description">The ruins of the Endless have an identifiable architecture; though they come in many styles certain qualities and materials unite them. Though now you find some that even by the standards of the Endless are strange - and ancient.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06_1Title">HOSTILE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06_1Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06_2Title">SELFISH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06_2Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06_3Title">HELPFUL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_06_3Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_07Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_07Description">Though your colonists place their first city not far from an ancient ruin - with access to water and flat land it is logical - something about the ruins are odd and unusually alien.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_08Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_08Description">The colonists have discovered a strange field here, with rings of Dust laid out in a regular pattern. To what purpose...? The strangeness of alien worlds is sometimes unsettling.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_09Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_09Description">You have found an ancient battlefield of the Endless on this planet. Great buildings lie broken by something other than the ravages of time, and the ruins are unusually rich in Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_10Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_10Description">This planet is littered with fallen satellites that were once an energy source for the Virtual Endless. But what brought them crashing down from orbit remains a mystery.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_11Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_11Description">A geothermal energy plant is the only thing that remains of this Concrete Endless city; whatever brought their downfall apparently desired their source of energy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_12Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_12Description">The ruins here are strange indeed - there is nothing but Dust, scattered across certain areas of the planet as though great sculptures of that substance suddenly lost their cohesion and fell.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_13Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_13Description">The patterns of Dust you see on this planet are unlike any others. Clearly, there is a great more than suspected to this strange, misunderstood substance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_14Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_14Description">Ruins on this planet indicate some sort of massive siege on a mountaintop. Strangely, the mountain itself contains no ruins or remnants of civilization, just high concentrations of Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15Description">Artifacts strewn in the ruins show an ancient civilization existed. But the size and shape are like nothing you have seen before; and your scientists and archaeologists wonder what it may mean.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15_1Title">HOSTILE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15_1Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15_2Title">SELFISH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15_2Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15_3Title">HELPFUL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_15_3Description">Click this button to select this option.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_16Title">DISCOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizationEventAdvanced_16Description">In an otherwise peaceful valley your colonists find remains of artifacts strewn about haphazardly. But where are the ruins of the civilization that left these? Why does nothing but Dust remain?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_EVENTOVERLAY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignSpecialSlotsTitle">SPECIAL SLOTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignSpecialSlotsDescription">Available special slots of the selected ship class</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignInvasionMilitaryPowerTitle">INVASION MP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignInvasionMilitaryPowerDescription">Invasion Military Power of the selected ship design</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignEvadeTitle">EVADE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignEvadeDescription">Evasion score of the selected ship design</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignAccuracyTitle">ACCURACY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipDesignAccuracyDescription">Accuracy score of the selected ship design</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryShipModuleSpecialSlotsDescription">Available special slots of the selected ship module</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DesignInvalidSpecialSlotTonnageDescription">You have exceeded the special slots quantity for this ship class.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModule,DefenseModuleFamilyTitle">WEAPON &amp; DEFENSE MODULES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModule,DefenseModuleFamilyDescription">All weapon and defense modules you have researched and unlocked</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecMod">SPECIAL MODULES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleFamilyDescription">All special modules you have researched and unlocked</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionMilitaryPowerDescription">Sort your fleets by invasion military power</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipDescription">This will repair the selected ships and modules to their full health for $DustCost Ḙ and $PopulationCost Ḛ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipEmptySelectionDescription">No ships have been selected.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipHarmonyDescription">The Harmony does not repair ships. When a rock breaks, it can only be replaced.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipFullHealthDescription">The selected ships do not require repair.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipOrbitDescription">The selected ships are not in orbit around one of your systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipSystemOwnerDescription">The selected ships need to be in orbit around one of your systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipSystemOwnershipDescription">The selected ships are in orbit around a system that is not 100% under your control.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipSystemLockedDescription">There is an ongoing battle around the system; repairs cannot be carried out properly.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipNoPopulationDescription">You need $PopulationCost Ḛ to repair the selected ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipNoDustDescription">You need $DustCost Ḙ to repair the selected ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipPopulationOnlyDescription">This will repair the selected ships and modules to their full health for $PopulationCost Ḛ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipDustOnlyDescription">This will repair the selected ships and modules to their full health for $DustCost Ḙ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipsConfirmation">Do you really want to repair your ships? It will cost you $DustCost Ḙ and $PopulationCost Ḛ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipsConfirmationPopulationOnly">Do you really want to repair your ships? It will cost you $PopulationCost Ḛ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RepairShipsConfirmationDustOnly">Do you really want to repair your ships? It will cost you  $DustCost Ḙ</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MILITARY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionReportEventInvaderSideFailFormat">YOUR INVASION OF $InvadedEmpire FAILED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionReportEventDefenderSideFailFormat">$InvadingEmpire FAILED TO CAPTURE YOUR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionReportEventInvaderSideSuccessFormat">INVASION SUCCEED! - OWNERSHIP: $Ownership</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionReportEventDefenderSideSuccessFormat">YOUR SYSTEM HAS BEEN CAPTURED BY $InvadingEmpire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LandInvasionReportTitle">LAND INVASION REPORT: $System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LandInvasionReportEventTooltipTitle">LAND INVASION REPORT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombingReportTitle">BOMBING REPORT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombingReportEventTooltipTitle">BOMBING REPORT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportEventInvaderLossesFormat">INVADER LOSSES ($InvadingEmpire)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportEventInvaderLossesDescription">Losses of the invader</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportEventDefenderLossesFormat">DEFENDER LOSSES ($InvadedEmpire)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportEventDefenderLossesDescription">Losses of the defender</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombingReportEventInvaderSideSuccessFormat">YOU HAVE SUCCESSFULLY STRICKEN THE $InvadedEmpire SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombingReportEventDefenderSideSuccessFormat">YOUR SYSTEM HAS BEEN STRICKEN BY $InvadingEmpire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombingReportEventInvaderSideFormat">ON $System SYSTEM ($InvadedEmpire)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombingReportEventDefenderSideFormat">ON $System SYSTEM BY $InvadingEmpire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombSelectionPanelTitle">BOMB SELECTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombKillPopulationTitle">INCAPACITATING
AGENTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombKillPopulationDescription">Rather than simply kill, these bombs are designed to hospitalize a population. A far greater weight on resources, they are morally humane but financially ruinous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombDestroyImprovementsTitle">CLUSTER
BOMBS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombDestroyImprovementsDescription">These bombs use advanced technology for both their propulsion and their avoidance systems. Randomly selecting the most vulnerable targets, they drop to a planet's surface and destroy existing infrastructure.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelFightersAndBombersTitle">FIGHTERS &amp; BOMBERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelLostFightersAndBombersDescription">List of the destroyed and remaining fighters and bombers</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelBombersTitle">BOMBERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelLostBombersDescription">List of the destroyed and remaining bombers</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelFightersTitle">FIGHTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelLostFightersDescription">List of the destroyed and remaining fighters</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelTroopsTitle">TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelLostTroopsDescription">List of the destroyed and remaining troops</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelLostImprovementsDescription">List of the destroyed and remaining improvements</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelLostPopulationDescription">List of the destroyed and remaining population</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ReportPanelRemaining">REMAINING:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScrapShipsConfirmationSingle">Destroying the selected ship will generate $Dust Ḙ.
Are you sure you want to destroy it permanently?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScrapShipsConfirmationPlural">Destroying all selected ships will generate $Dust Ḙ.
Are you sure you want to destroy them permanently?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScrapBuildingsConfirmationSingle">Destroying the selected building will generate $Dust Ḙ.
Are you sure you want to scrap it permanently?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScrapBuildingsConfirmationPlural">Destroying the selected buildings will generate $Dust Ḙ.
Are you sure you want to scrap them permanently?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MESSAGES" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlaceholderEffectTooltip">$(Warning) PLACEHOLDER: THIS ITEM HAS NO EFFECT YET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementTitle">IMPROVEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemImprovementTitle">IMPROVEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassStarSystemImprovementTooltipEffectTitle">IMPROVEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemBonusTitle">MAIN SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireApprovalStatusTitle">EMPIRE APPROVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireApprovalStatusFerventCompoundTitle">EMPIRE (WITH APPROVAL: FERVENT)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireApprovalStatusContentCompoundTitle">EMPIRE (WITH APPROVAL: CONTENT)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireApprovalStatusUnhappyCompoundTitle">EMPIRE (WITH APPROVAL: UNHAPPY)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireApprovalStatusRebellionCompoundTitle">EMPIRE (WITH APPROVAL: REBELLION)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ApprovalStatusTitle">SYSTEM APPROVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemApprovalStatusEcstaticCompoundTitle">SYSTEM (WITH APPROVAL: ECSTATIC)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemApprovalStatusHappyCompoundTitle">SYSTEM (WITH APPROVAL: HAPPY)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemApprovalStatusContentCompoundTitle">SYSTEM (WITH APPROVAL: CONTENT)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemApprovalStatusUnhappyCompoundTitle">SYSTEM (WITH APPROVAL: UNHAPPY)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemApprovalStatusStrikeCompoundTitle">SYSTEM (WITH APPROVAL: STRIKE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BaseApprovalTitle">EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OverPopulationTitle">OVERPOPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OverPopulationApprovalTitle">OVERPOPULATION DISAPPROVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OverColonizationApprovalTitle">EXPANSION DISAPPROVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CurrentOwnershipTitle">OWNERSHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RegenerationBonusTitle">OWNERSHIP GAIN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OwnershipGainBonusTitle">OWNERSHIP GAIN PER SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OwnershipLossBonusTitle">OWNERSHIP LOSS PER SYSTEM CAPTURED BY OPPONENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassEmpireCompoundTitle">EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassStarSystemCompoundTitle">SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassTitle">SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassSystemTitle">SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassPlanetCompoundTitle">PLANETS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassMoonCompoundTitle">MOONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetInfrastructureTitle">INFRASTRUCTURE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassStarSystemImprovementCompoundTitle">IMPROVEMENTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FoodSurplusBonusTitle">FOOD SURPLUS BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FoodConsumptionTitle">FOOD CONSUMPTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FoodPerPopTitle">FOOD CONSUMPTION PER POP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryTitle">INDUSTRY CONVERSION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TaxBonusTitle">TAX RATE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TaxBonusHarmonyValueTitle">Value: $TaxRatePercent%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BuildingIndustryCostDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY (Building Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechnoCostDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY (Research Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipIndustryCostDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY (Ship Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UpkeepHeroDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY (Hero Upkeep)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UpkeepShipDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY (Ship Upkeep)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UpkeepConstructionDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY (Construction Upkeep)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OverPopApprovalDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponDamageDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseEfficiencyDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FIDSDifficultyFactorTitle">GAME DIFFICULTY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BuildingIndustryCostSpeedFactorTitle">SPEED FACTOR (Building Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipIndustryCostSpeedFactorTitle">SPEED FACTOR (Ship Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechnoCostSpeedFactorTitle">SPEED FACTOR (Research Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CostSpeedFactorTitle">SPEED FACTOR (Cost)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GameSpeedFactorTitle">CURRENT GAME SPEED </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FoodRequiredSpeedFactorTitle">SPEED FACTOR (Food Consumption)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechnoCostBonusTitle">RESEARCH COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitTitle">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle05Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle06Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitSpaceBattle07Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet05Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet06Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitFleet07Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense05Title">SOLID CITIZENS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy07Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy09Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy13Title">EFFICIENT STOCK</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm1TooltipEffect1">COLONIZES ALL PLANETS (-50% $(FIDS) UNTIL REQUIRED TECH KNOWN)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm1TooltipEffect2">AS HARMONY -8% GROWTH PER COLONIZED PLANET UNTIL REQUIRED TECH KNOWN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm1TooltipEffect3">AS SOWER -25% $(Approval) LOSS FROM PLANET UNTIL REQUIRED TECH KNOWN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm1TooltipEffect4">-50% $(Approval) LOSS FROM PLANET ONCE REQUIRED TECH KNOWN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm2TooltipEffect1">COLONIZES ALL PLANETS (-25% $(FIDS) UNTIL TECH UNLOCKED)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm2TooltipEffect2">AS HARMONY -4% GROWTH PER COLONIZED PLANET UNTIL REQUIRED TECH KNOWN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm2TooltipEffect3">AS SOWER -50% $(Approval) LOSS FROM PLANET UNTIL REQUIRED TECH KNOWN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Norm2TooltipEffect4">-50% $(Approval) LOSS FROM PLANET ONCE REQUIRED TECH KNOWN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WithColonizeTraitScience03TooltipEffect">REMOVE THE COLONIZATION PENALTY ON THAT PLANET TYPE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03TerranTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Terran)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03JungleTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Jungle)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03OceanTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Ocean)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03AridTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Arid)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03TundraTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Tundra)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03DesertTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Desert)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03ArcticTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Arctic)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03LavaTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Lava)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03BarrenTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Barren)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03GasGiantTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Gas Giant)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03GasHydrogenTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Gas Hydrogen)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03GasHeliumTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Gas Helium)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03GasMethaneTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Gas Methane)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience03AsteroidsTitle">FACTION TRAIT (Asteroids)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitPopulation01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitPopulation02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitPopulation03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitPopulation04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitBuilding01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitBuilding02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitBuilding03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEvent01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEvent02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDiplomacy01Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDiplomacy02Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDiplomacy03Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDiplomacy04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemOwnerTitle">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxHeroesTitle">ACADEMY CAP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilitiesTitle">HERO ABILITIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AbilityPointTitle">ABILITY POINT(S)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassHeroCompoundTitle">HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroXPPerBattleTitle">HERO XP PER BATTLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TurnsBeforeNewHeroTitle">TURN(S) BEFORE NEW HERO ARRIVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%XPPerAssignedTurnBonusTitle">XP BONUS WHEN ASSIGNED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%XPPerBattleBonusTitle">XP BONUS FOR EACH BATTLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%XPPerConstructionBonusTitle">XP BONUS FOR EACH CONSTRUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%XPPerEnnemyInjuredBonusTitle">XP BONUS FOR EACH OPPONENT INJURED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AssignationDelayLimitTitle">TURNS TO MOVE A HERO FROM ITS CURRENT ASSIGNMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExtraClonesAllowedTitle">EXTRA CLONES ALLOWED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DustTermBonusTitle">DIPLOMATIC TERMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleRepairRateTitle">MODULE REGENERATION (IN ALL AREAS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleRepairRateAlliedTitle">MODULE REGENERATION (INSIDE FRIENDLY AREA)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HealingTitle">HP REGENERATION (IN ALL AREAS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HealingPercentTitle">HP REGENERATION PERCENT (IN ALL AREAS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HealingAlliedTitle">HP REGENERATION (INSIDE FRIENDLY AREA)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HealingPercentAlliedTitle">HP REGENERATION PERCENT (INSIDE FRIENDLY AREA)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonusTitle">DIPLOMATIC TERMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementCountTitle">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_2Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_3Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_4Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_5Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_6Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_7Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_8Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementBonus_0_9Title">COOPERATION TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NumberOfFriendsTitle">FACTION AT PEACE OR ALLIED WITH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UnarmedShipCostBonusTitle">SHIP COST FOR SHIP WITHOUT WEAPON MODULE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetTypeTooltipEffectTitle">PLANET TYPE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%From">FROM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%To">ON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Per">PER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectDurationSingleFormat">(#33CDFF#1 TURN#REVERT#)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectDurationPluralFormat">(#33CDFF#$Value TURNS#REVERT#)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectFrequencySingleFormat">EVERY TURN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectFrequencyPluralFormat">EVERY $Value TURNS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeOtherEmpiresTitle">FOR OTHER EMPIRES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeAllEmpiresTitle">FOR ALL EMPIRES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeAlliesTitle">FOR ALLIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeEnemiesTitle">FOR ENEMIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeRandomEmpireTitle">FOR AN EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeRandomAllyTitle">FOR AN ALLY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EffectScopeRandomEnemyTitle">FOR AN ENEMY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoneyTitle">RAW INCOME</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UpkeepTitle">UPKEEP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroInitialXPTitle">HERO XP ON HIRING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipInitialXPTitle">SHIP XP ON BUILDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipCostBonusTitle">SHIP COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IdleShipXPPerTurnTitle">SHIP XP PER TURN IF SHIP IDLED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxCommandPointTitle">COMMAND POINTS CAP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassShipCompoundTitle">SHIPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassFleetCompoundTitle">FLEETS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetWormholeUnlockTitle">UNLOCKS SPACE TRAVELS VIA WORMHOLES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetWormhole2UnlockTitle">WORMHOLES IN YOUR POSSESSION ARE LINKED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetFreeMovementUnlockTitle">UNLOCKS SPACE TRAVEL WITHOUT COSMIC STRING OR WORMHOLE USE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ImprovementCostBonusTitle">INDUSTRY COST OF IMPROVEMENTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageMaxTitle">DAMAGE MAX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamageMinTitle">DAMAGE MIN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionRegenerationBonusTitle">CONTROL RECOVERY (INVASION)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemInvasionDefenseTitle">SYSTEM DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScienceBonusPerCPAfterEncounterTitle">RESEARCH POINTS TO THE CURRENT RESEARCH FOR EACH DESTROYED ENEMY CP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DustBonusPerCPAfterEncounterTitle">DUST FOR EACH DESTROYED ENEMY CP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeflectedPerTurnTitle">KINETIC PROJECTILES DEFLECTED PER ROUND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeflectionPerTurnTitle">KINETIC PROJECTILES DEFLECTED PER ROUND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AccuracyTitle">ACCURACY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AbsorptionTitle">LASER DAMAGE ABSORBED PER ROUND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CriticChanceTitle">CRITIC CHANCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CriticMultiplierTitle">CRITIC MULTIPLIER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TurnBeforeReachTitle">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InterceptionEvasionTitle">INTERCEPTION EVASION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InterceptionAccuracyTitle">INTERCEPTION ACCURACY ON ONE MISSILE PER ROUND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NumberPerSalveTitle">PROJECTILES PER SALVO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TurnToReloadTitle">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LaserCompoundTitle">BEAM WEAPON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%KineticCompoundTitle">KINETIC WEAPON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MissileCompoundTitle">MISSILE WEAPON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BomberCompoundTitle">BOMBER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FighterCompoundTitle">FIGHTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleTroopsCompoundTitle">TROOPS MODULES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleRepairCompoundTitle">SUPPORT MODULE REPAIR </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleEngineCompoundTitle">SUPPORT MODULE ENGINE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleArmorCompoundTitle">SUPPORT MODULE ARMOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleCostBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULES COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModuleCostBonusTitle">WEAPON MODULE COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponFamilyCostBonusTitle">WEAPON FAMILY COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModuleWeightBonusTitle">WEAPON MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleArmorWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE ARMOR TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleInvasionWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE INVASION TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModulePowerWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE POWER TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleScoutWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE SCOUT TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleRepairWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE REPAIR TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleEngineWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE ENGINE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleCivilianWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE CIVILIAN TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleScoutCompoundTitle">SUPPORT MODULE SCOUT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleWeightBonusTitle">DEFENSE MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WonderScoreTitle">BUILDING 5 COPIES OF THIS IMPROVEMENT LEADS TO VICTORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HealingCostBonusTitle">HEALING COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FatigueRecoveryPerTurnTitle">FATIGUE RECOVERY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TradeRoutesGainTitle">TRADE ROUTE GAINS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxTradeRoutesTitle">TRADE ROUTES CAP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TradeRoutesBonusesTitle">TRADE ROUTES BONUSES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TradeRoutesDistanceBonusFactorTitle">TRADE ROUTES DISTANCE BONUSES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TradeRoutesDustBonusTitle">TRADE ROUTE DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InfluenceTitle">INFLUENCE AREA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseTitle">DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OverheadPopulationTitle">MOVABLE POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationTitle">POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxPopulationTitle">MAX POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxSystemPopulationTitle">MAX POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetPopulationStatusTitle">POPULATION STATUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetColonizationStatusTitle">COLONIZED PLANET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LocustPointsTitle">LOCUST POINTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LocustPointsUpdatePerTurnTitle">LOCUST POINTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassPlanet,PlanetColonizationStatusLocustTitle">PLANET (CRAVING)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonizedModifierTitle">PLANET STATUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetStatusTitle">PLANET STATUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoonStatusExploredCompoundTitle">EXPLORED MOON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoonStatusExploredWithTempleCompoundTitle">EXPLORED MOON WITH TEMPLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AnomalyReductionTooltipEffect">ANOMALY'S EFFECTS REPLACED BY:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AnomalyReductionNoEffectTooltipEffect">NO EFFECT ON PLANET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TempleTitle">TEMPLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MonopolyBonusTitle">MONOPOLY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceMonopolyEffectsTitle">EFFECTS IF RESOURCE MONOPOLY ($Units+):</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceAbundanceEffectsTitle">EFFECTS IF RESOURCE ABUNDANCE ($Units+):</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DepositSizeTitle">DEPOSIT SIZE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceDepositStrategicCompoundTitle">EACH STRATEGIC RESOURCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceDepositLuxuryCompoundTitle">EACH LUXURY RESOURCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetStrategicResourceTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceFoodTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceScienceTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceIndustryTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceMoneyTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceFIDSBonusMultiplierTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCES' FIDS BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetQualityTitle">PLANET QUALITY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetQualityImprovedCompoundTitle">PLANET QUALITY (Improved)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetQualityDefaultCompoundTitle">PLANET QUALITY (Default)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetQualityDepletedCompoundTitle">PLANET QUALITY (Depleted)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StrategicResourcesForMonopolyTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCE REQUIRED FOR ABUNDANCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NumberOfStrategicResourcesTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCE DEPOSITS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceDepositTitle">RESOURCE DEPOSIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NegativeEventTitle">NEGATIVE EVENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NegativeFactionEventTitle">NEGATIVE EVENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalEventTitle">GLOBAL EVENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PositiveEventTitle">POSITIVE EVENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PositiveFactionEventTitle">POSITIVE EVENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScienceVictoryTechnoCostBonusTitle">SCIENTIFIC VICTORY RESEARCH COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipInitialHPBonusTitle">INITIAL SHIP HP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoneyLeechedTitle">DUST LEECHED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScienceLeechedTitle">SCIENCE LEECHED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoneyGatheredByLeechTitle">DUST GATHERED BY LEECH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScienceGatheredByLeechTitle">SCIENCE GATHERED BY LEECH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleCardCostBonusTitle">ABILITIES DUST COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AssignationDelayLimitTitle">TURNS TO BE MOVED FROM ITS CURRENT ASSIGNMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BypassBlockadeTitle">BLOCKADE BYPASS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemStatusTitle">BLOCKADED SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemStatusBlocusTitle">BLOCKADED SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemStatusBlocusCompoundTitle">BLOCKADED SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetBattleHealingTitle">FLEET HP PER BATTLE PHASE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetHealingAlliedTitle">FLEET HP PER TURN (FRIENDLY SECTOR)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleHealingPercentTitle">SHIP REPAIR PER BATTLE PHASE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetHealingPercentAlliedTitle">FLEET REPAIR PER TURN (FRIENDLY SECTOR)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleHealingTitle">SHIP HP PER BATTLE PHASE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetHealingTitle">FLEET HP PER TURN (ALL SECTORS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetBattleHealingPercentTitle">FLEET REPAIR PER BATTLE PHASE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetHealingPercentTitle">FLEET REPAIR PER TURN (ALL SECTORS)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WeaponModuleFleetTitle">FLEET WEAPONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleFleetTitle">FLEET DEFENSES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassShipFleetTitle">FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LaserFleetTitle">FLEET BEAM WEAPON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%KineticFleetTitle">FLEET KINETIC WEAPON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MissileFleetTitle">FLEET MISSILE WEAPON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MilitaryPowerInvasionTitle">INVASION MILITARY POWER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NumberOfAlliesTitle">NUMBER OF ALLIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NumberOfWarsTitle">NUMBER OF WARS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InAllianceTitle">ALLIANCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AlliedTerritoryDefenseBonusTitle">ALLIED TERRITORY DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FleetSpyingTitle">        + ABILITY TO SPY ALL FLEETS ORBITING THIS SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoneyLeechBonusTitle">DUST LEECH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScienceLeechBonusTitle">SCIENCE LEECH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BuyOutBonusTitle">BUYOUT BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BuyoutTitle">BUYOUT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CantBuyoutAffinityHarmony">The Harmony will not risk corruption from Dust to complete construction.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RetrofitInvalidHarmonyDescription">The Harmony will not use corrupted Dust to retrofit their ships.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryBoostTitle">EMPIRE IMPROVEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryApprovalTitle">APPROVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryFoodTitle">FOOD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryIndustryTitle">INDUSTRY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryMoneyTitle">DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryScienceTitle">SCIENCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryHeroXPTitle">HERO XP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryShipHPTitle">SHIP XP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryShipMovementBonusTitle">SHIP MOVEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryShipXPTitle">SHIP XP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryFIDSBonusMultiplierTitle">LUXURY BASE FIDS BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryFIDSTitle">FIDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FoodTitle">FOOD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IndustryTitle">INDUSTRY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoneyTitle">DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScienceTitle">SCIENCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IndustryToScienceConversionFactorTitle">INDUSTRY TO SCIENCE CONVERSION FACTOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryTradeRouteBonusTitle">TRADE ROUTE BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryBuyOutBonusTitle">BUYOUT BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryInvasionTitle">INVASION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryHealingTitle">HEALING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryShipAttackTitle">SHIP ATTACK</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LuxuryShipDefenseTitle">SHIP DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IndustryOverProductionBonusTitle">INDUSTRY OVERPRODUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FoodSurplusToProductionBonusTitle">CONVERTED FOOD SURPLUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonyExpansionLimiterTitle">DISTANCE WITH EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierPeacefulTitle">DUE TO A LONG TERM PEACEFUL STATUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierCooperationAgreementTitle">DUE TO COOPERATION AGREEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierAllianceTitle">DUE TO ALLIANCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierCommonEnemyTitle">DUE TO A COMMON ENEMY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierCommonFriendsTitle">DUE TO A COMMON FRIEND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierCurrentExchangesTitle">DUE TO CURRENT EXCHANGES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierPastExchangesTitle">DUE TO PAST EXCHANGES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierCooperationAgreementTreatyTitle">DUE TO A COOPERATION AGREEMENT TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierOpenBordersTreatyTitle">DUE TO AN OPEN BORDERS TREATY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierDonationsTitle">DUE TO DONATIONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierWarTitle">DUE TO WAR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierCeaseFireTitle">DUE TO CEASE FIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierPastWarTitle">DUE TO PAST WAR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierWarpLinkTenseFrontiersTitle">DUE TO TENSE FRONTIERS (WARP LINK)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierWormholeLinkTenseFrontiersTitle">DUE TO TENSE FRONTIERS (WORMHOLE LINK)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierAnotherAllianceTitle">DUE TO ANOTHER ALLIANCE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierBrokenExchangeTitle">DUE TO BROKEN EXCHANGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierPropositionRefusalTitle">DUE TO PROPOSITION REFUSAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierOwningLegitimateTerritoryTitle">DUE TO INVASION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierLivingSpaceTenseTitle">DUE TO EXPANSION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierScoreTenseTitle">DUE TO SCORE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierMilitaryPowerWeaknessStressTitle">DUE TO MILITARY WEAKNESS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierMilitaryPowerRespectTitle">DUE TO RESPECT FOR YOUR MILITARY STRENGTH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierMilitaryPowerPityTitle">DUE TO APPRECIATION FOR YOUR PACIFIST RESTRAINT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierMilitaryPowerTenseTitle">DUE TO CONCERNS OVER YOUR MILITARY BUILD-UP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierSecuringNeighbourhoodTitle">DUE TO AN ONGOING WAR WITH ANOTHER FACTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierMilitaryBalanceTitle">DUE TO THE PROPORTIONS OF YOUR MILITARY INVESTMENTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAttitudeModifierConnectionSpaceTenseTitle">DUE TO TENSION OVER CONNECTIONS BETWEEN STAR SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ContractRefusedByAITitle">Your proposition has been rejected:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OpenBordersTermRefusedTitle">You wish to travel freely within our borders, but we are not ready for this;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DeclareWarTermRefusedTitle">We are not prepared to join you in war;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CeaseFireTermRefusedTitle">We do not feel it is time for a cease fire;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeaceTermRefusedTitle">We are not prepared to make peace with you;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreateAllianceTermRefusedTitle">We are not ready to form an alliance with you;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LeaveAllianceTermRefusedTitle">We do not feel it is appropriate to leave this alliance; </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InviteToAllianceTermRefusedTitle">You are kind to ask us, but we would not join your alliance;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementTermRefusedTitle">The terms of this cooperation agreement are not pleasing to us;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DustInstantaneousTermRefusedTitle">We will not accept this Dust from you;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DustPerTurnTermRefusedTitle">We do not want this Dust income from you;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechnologyTermRefusedTitle">Your offer to exchange technology is not acceptable;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemTermRefusedTitle">Trading this star system is not of interest to us;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceTermRefusedTitle">Our people are not in favor of this resource trade;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DealPriceToLowRefusedTitle">The price you seem to find acceptable is not acceptable to us;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticStatusConditionInvalidTitle">Standard diplomatic conditions and our mutual relations do not permit this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AttitudeConditionInvalidTitle">Our peoples have not yet learned to trust each other.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AttitudeTrendConditionInvalidTitle">Our relations are not improving.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleRatioConditionInvalidTitle">Our fleets are not in a situation that puts us at ease.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarFatigueConditionInvalidTitle">Our people are not yet ready to give up their struggle.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BetterMilitaryPowerConditionInvalidTitle">Your military power does not leave us trembling.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IAmAttackerConditionInvalidTitle">We are hardly the aggressors in this conflict.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeriodOfNonAggressionConditionInvalidTitle">More time in a neutral status is necessary before we are ready for this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AtWarConditionInvalidTitle">We are sufficiently involved in war as it is.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarRatioConditionInvalidTitle">Our conflicts are not evolving in a way that suits us.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ConquestRatioConditionInvalidTitle">Conflicts and control of systems are not evolving in a way that suits us.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AtAllianceConditionInvalidTitle">We need to be allies before this type of proposal would be appropriate.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticStatusDescription">Standard diplomatic conditions and mutual relations do not permit this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AttitudeDescription">The attitude does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AttitudeTrendDescription">The attitude trend does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BattleRatioDescription">The MP loss ratio does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarFatigueDescription">You have not been at war long enough to allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BetterMilitaryPowerDescription">The military power does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IAmAttackerDescription">The fact that you are the aggressor does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PeriodOfNonAggressionDescription">You have not been diplomatically neutral long enough to permit this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AtWarDescription">The faction's status (war) does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WarRatioDescription">The MP and system loss ratio does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ConquestRatioDescription">The system loss ratio does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AtAllianceDescription">The faction's status (alliance) does not allow this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WaitingPeriodDescription">It is too soon to change the terms of an agreement; your word will not be trusted if you do so.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TermRejectDescription">We must refuse your offer;</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TermCanNotBeOfferedDescription">The terms you request cannot be fulfilled.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreditorHaveToMuchMoneyDescription">You already have a healthy pile of cash, and the other faction doesn't think you need more.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreditorHaveToMuchRevenueDescription">The other faction believes that you have a rich revenue stream, and don't really need more.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreditorHaveToBadAttitudeTowardDebtorDescription">They don't like you all that much, and they're not sure they want your money.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CreditorHaveToMuchScienceDescription">Your level of science is advanced, and they don't think you need money as well.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorIsNotAfraidOfCreditorDescription">You do not inspire enough fear for them to feel they should give you money.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorHaveBetterMilitaryPowerThanCreditorDescription">Their military is superior, and they see no need to bow to your request.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorHaveNotEnoughInstanceOfThisResourceDescription">There are not enough deposits of the resource to make this trade.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorHaveToEnoughMoneyDescription">The other faction feels financially secure enough to reject your offer.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorHaveToBadAttitudeTowardCreditorDescription">The other faction just plain dislikes you too much to want to give you anything.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemIsToFarFromTheCreditorEmpireDescription">The other faction is not interested by trading this system as it will greatly expand your empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorIsWinningTheWarDescription">The other faction has the feeling to win the war and will give you nothing.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NotOverMyDeadBodyDescription">The feeling of the other faction could be summed up as "Over my dead body/mechanism/exoskeleton/pod."</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DebtorHaveNotEnoughMoneyDescription">When comparing their treasury to yours, the other faction thinks you should be giving Dust away, not getting more!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize2TooltipEffect">+1 $(CommandPoint) PER NEW SHIP CLASS UNLOCKED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MaxFleetSize2SwarmTooltipEffect">+2 $(CommandPoint) IF ALL SHIP CLASSES UNLOCKED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassLarge1EmperorCompoundTitle">SHIPS OF CLASS 'DREADNOUGHT'</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementFood3TooltipEffect">      +3 $(Food) PER $(Population) ON PLANETS WITH AN EXPLORED MOON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementFood3SowerTooltipEffect2">      +3 $(Industry) PER $(Population) ON PLANETS WITH A TEMPLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1TooltipEffect1">+8 $(Money) PER COLONIZED TERRAN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1TooltipEffect2">+8 $(Money) PER COLONIZED JUNGLE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1TooltipEffect3">+8 $(Money) PER COLONIZED OCEAN</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1TooltipEffect4">+8 $(Money) PER COLONIZED ARID</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney1TooltipEffect5">+8 $(Money) PER COLONIZED TUNDRA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementMoney2TooltipEffect">      +2 $(Money) PER $(Population) ON PLANETS WITH AN EXPLORED MOON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementIndustry6TooltipEffect">100% $(Food) SURPLUS CONVERTED INTO $(Industry)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience5TooltipEffect">50% $(Industry) OVERPRODUCTION CONVERTED INTO $(Science)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementHabitat2TooltipEffect">       +1 $(MaxPopulation) ON PLANETS WITH AN EXPLORED MOON</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToScienceTooltipEffect">33% $(Industry) CONVERTED INTO $(Science)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToDustTooltipEffect">33% $(Industry) CONVERTED INTO $(Money)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToFoodSowerTooltipEffect">33% $(Industry) CONVERTED INTO $(Food)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToFoodHarmonyTooltipEffect">33% $(Industry) CONVERTED INTO $(Food)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionDustToScienceSophonTooltipEffect">200% $(Money) CONVERTED INTO $(Science)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionScienceToDustEmperorTooltipEffect">200% $(Science) CONVERTED INTO $(Money)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToScienceSophonTooltipEffect">INCREASES IND-SCIENCE CONVERSION FROM 33% $(Industry) TO 50% $(Industry)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemConversionIndustryToDustTerranTooltipEffect">INCREASES IND-DUST CONVERSION FROM 33% $(Industry) TO 50% $(Industry)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementBuildingVictoryTooltipEffect2">      +2 $(Approval) ON EACH SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemColonialBaseTooltipEffect1">+5 $(Industry) PER PLANET COLONIZED ON SYSTEM </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemColonialBaseTooltipEffect2">+5 $(Food) PER PLANET COLONIZED ON SYSTEM </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityTitle">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityMappingTitle">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityAmoebaTooltipEffect">STARTS WITH THE WHOLE MAP KNOWN: SYSTEMS, WARPS, WORMHOLES AND HOME WORLDS ARE REVEALED.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHoratioTooltipEffect">UNLOCKS THE CLONING OF A HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityTerranTooltipEffect">      0%-100% TAX RATE WILL GIVE A 0%-60% $(Industry) BONUS.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinitySophonTooltipEffect">      0%-50% TAX RATE WILL GIVE A 50%-0% $(Science) BONUS.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinitySwarmTooltipEffect1">+1 LOCUST POINT PER TURN ON EACH COLONIZED PLANET.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinitySwarmTooltipEffect2">+25% FIDS FOR THE FIRST 40 LP, -25% AFTER 60.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinitySowerTooltipEffect1">       -50% $(Food) FROM SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinitySowerTooltipEffect2">       30% OF $(Industry) VALUE IS ALSO ADDED TO $(Food)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTooltipEffect1">DOESN'T USE DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTooltipEffect2">IS NOT AFFECTED BY APPROVAL MODIFIERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTooltipEffect3">$(Money) GENERATES LOSS OF $(Science) AND $(Food) ON SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTooltipEffect4">DISHARMONY: DECREASES FIS ON EMPIRE FOR EACH "IMPURE" SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DustCorruptionMultiplierTitle">EMPIRE SIZE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Norm1TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET IS MINERAL RICH.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Norm2TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET HAS RICH SOIL.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Norm3TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET HAS A POSITIVE ANOMALY.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Alt1TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET IS MINERAL POOR.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Alt2TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET HAS POOR SOIL.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy05Alt3TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET HAS A NEGATIVE ANOMALY.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy07Norm1TooltipEffect1">       • TRADE ROUTES ALSO WORK IN COLD WAR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy07Norm1TooltipEffect2">       • BLOCKADES ON YOUR SYSTEMS WON'T BREAK TRADE ROUTES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy08Norm1TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET HAS METALLIC WATERS.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy08Norm2TooltipEffect">       • THE HOME PLANET HAS METALLIC WATERS.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy10Norm1TooltipEffect">       +20 $(Money) AT START</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy10Norm2TooltipEffect">       +42 $(Money) AT START</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy10Alt1TooltipEffect">       NO $(Money) AT START</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy14TooltipEffect1">+50% LUXURY BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitEconomy14AltTooltipEffect1">-50% LUXURY BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm1TooltipEffect1">AFTER LOSING A SYSTEM:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm1TooltipEffect2">       • +25% Ḷ ON ALL FLEETS WHEN INVADING (FOR 20 TURNS).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm1TooltipEffect3">       • +25% GROUND DEFENSE ON ALL SYSTEMS (FOR 20 TURNS).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm1SystemLostTitle">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm2TooltipEffect1">AFTER LOSING A SYSTEM:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm2TooltipEffect2">       • +50% Ḷ ON ALL FLEETS WHEN INVADING (FOR 20 TURNS).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm2TooltipEffect3">       • +50% GROUND DEFENSE ON ALL SYSTEMS (FOR 20 TURNS).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitDefense04Norm2SystemLostTitle">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero03Norm1TooltipEffect">-2 UPKEEP ON HEROES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero03Norm2TooltipEffect">-4 UPKEEP ON HEROES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero03Alt1TooltipEffect">1 COSTLESS ABILITY POINT ON HEROES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero03Alt2TooltipEffect">2 COSTLESS ABILITY POINTS ON HEROES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero04Norm1TooltipEffect">THE HERO WILL BE INJURED IF YOU USE THE "RETREAT" BATTLE ACTION.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero04Norm2TooltipEffect">THE HERO WILL BE INJURED IF YOU USE THE "RETREAT" BATTLE ACTION.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHero05Title">DUST CONGRUITY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvisibleForEnnemiesTitle">       • ABILITY TO HIDE FROM OPPONENT INSPECTION ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityCommander05TooltipEffect1">+3% DAMAGE PER SHIP CLASS ON FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityCommander05TooltipEffect2">+1% DEFENSE PER SHIP CLASS ON FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityCommander01TooltipEffect">-6% ACCURACY TO ENEMY WEAPONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityCommander02TooltipEffect">-7% ACCURACY TO ENEMY WEAPONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityCommander03TooltipEffect">+25% HERO OFFENSE AND DEFENSE ATTRIBUTES DURING A BATTLE IF THE ENEMY FLEET HAS A HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityAdventurer02TooltipEffect">       +0.25% DUST LEECH PER LEVEL ON HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityAdventurer03TooltipEffect">       +0.5% DUST LEECH PER LEVEL ON HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityAdventurer04TooltipEffect">THE PLAYER CAN BENEFIT FROM OTHER FACTION'S DETECTION RADIUS, WHILE IN ORBIT OF AN OTHER FACTION'S SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityAdventurer08TooltipEffect">       +0.25% SCIENCE LEECH PER LEVEL ON HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroAbilityAdventurer12TooltipEffect">       +0.5% SCIENCE LEECH PER LEVEL ON HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementStep1TooltipEffect"> 0-10 TURNS: -50% ON TRADE ROUTES EFFECTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementStep2TooltipEffect">10-15 TURNS: 0% ON TRADE ROUTES EFFECTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CooperationAgreementStep3TooltipEffect">AFTER 15 TURNS: +25% ON TRADE ROUTES EFFECTS </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OverProductionToStackFactorTitle">OVER PRODUCTION TO STACK FACTOR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StackedOverProductionInterestsPerTurnTitle">INTERESTS FOR STACKED INDUSTRY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4AutomatonTooltipEffect">STACKED INDUSTRY WILL BE ADDED TO THE SYSTEM DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense6TooltipEffect1">+1% INVASION RECOVERY FOR EACH FRIENDLY SHIP ORBITING ON STAR SYSTEM (UP TO 10%)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience7TooltipEffect1">+250 DEFENSE PER COLONIZED ASTEROID</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience7TooltipEffect2">+40 $(Science) PER COLONIZED ASTEROID</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueAutomatonTooltipEffect1">+1% $(Food) FOR EACH OF YOUR SHIP ORBITING ON STAR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueAutomatonTooltipEffect2">+1% $(Industry) FOR EACH OF YOUR SHIP ORBITING ON STAR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueAutomatonTooltipEffect3">+1% $(Money) FOR EACH OF YOUR SHIP ORBITING ON STAR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueAutomatonTooltipEffect4">+1% $(Science) FOR EACH OF YOUR SHIP ORBITING ON STAR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueHarmonyTooltipEffect">+50% FIS ON PLANET WITH $(Population) MAX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementTrade1TooltipEffect1">-15% UPKEEP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyTooltipEffect1">33% $(Money) CONVERTED INTO $(Food)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyTooltipEffect2">33% $(Money) CONVERTED INTO $(Science)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyTooltipEffect3">NO $(Money) PRODUCED ON COLONIZED PLANET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyTooltipEffect4">PURIFICATION OF THE STAR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense4HarmonyTooltipEffect5">THIS IMPROVEMENT CANNOT BE SCRAPPED OR RAZED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectXpBonusHeroContextFormat">       +$Value XP ON HERO: #33CDFF#$HeroName#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectXpBonusHeroContextInvalidFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOU HAVE NO HERO IN YOUR FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectXpBonusShipContextFormat">       +$Value XP ON FLEET: #33CDFF#$FleetName#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectXpBonusShipContextInvalidFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOUR FLEET HAS DISAPPEARED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectShipSabotageContextFormat">       $Value% HP ON FLEET: #33CDFF#$FleetName#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectShipSabotageContextInvalidFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOUR FLEET HAS DISAPPEARED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectExpelHeroContextFormat">THE FOLLOWING HERO WILL BE FIRED: #33CDFF#$HeroName#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectExpelHeroContextInvalidFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOU HAVE NO HERO IN YOUR FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectModifyPopulationAddEmpireFormat">$PopCount$(Population) ON EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectModifyPopulationRemoveEmpireFormat">$PopCount$(Population) ON EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectNewColonyShipFormat">A NEW COLONY SHIP IS CREATED $Orbit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnNewShipScoutFormat">A NEW EXPLORATION SHIP IS CREATED $Orbit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnNewShipDefenderFormat">A NEW DEFENSE SHIP IS CREATED $Orbit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnNewShipColonyFormat">A NEW COLONY SHIP IS CREATED $Orbit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnNewShipAdvancedFormat">A NEW ADVANCED DEFENSE SHIP IS CREATED $Orbit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnOrbitHomeSystemFormat">ON THE PLAYER'S HOME SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnOrbitLastSystemFormat">ON THE PLAYER'S LATEST COLONIZED SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectSpawnOrbitExploredSystemFormat">ON $System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectStartingSystemHomeSystemFormat">OF THE PLAYER'S HOME SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectStartingSystemLastSystemFormat">OF THE PLAYER'S LATEST COLONIZED SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectStartingSystemExploredSystemFormat">OF $System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectAbilityPointsBonusHeroContextFormat">ABILITY POINT(S) ON HERO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectAbilityPointsBonusHeroContextSingleFormat">$Point ABILITY POINT IS AVAILABLE TO SPEND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectAbilityPointsBonusHeroContextPluralFormat">$Point ABILITY POINTS ARE AVAILABLE TO SPEND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectAbilityPointsBonusHeroContextInvalidFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOU HAVE NO HERO IN YOUR FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectAbilityPointsBonusHeroContextInvalidSingleFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOU HAVE NO HERO IN YOUR FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AchievementEffectAbilityPointsBonusHeroContextInvalidPluralFormat">THIS DISCOVERY WILL HAVE NO EFFECT AS YOU HAVE NO HERO IN YOUR FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetNaturalWonder08TooltipEffect">       -30% UPKEEP ON STAR SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ExpansionLossTitle">EXPANSION EFFORT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TaxBonusHarmonyCategoryTitle">Food/Science Distribution</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TaxBonusHarmonyDescription">Distribution of Empire's resources between Food and Science. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageAgainstPopulationTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageOnPopulationMultiplierTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageAgainstImprovementsTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST IMPROVEMENTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageOnImprovementsMultiplierTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST IMPROVEMENTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageAgainstSubShipsTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST AIRCRAFT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageOnSubShipsMultiplierTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST AIRCRAFT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageAgainstTroopsTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CollateralDamageOnTroopsMultiplierTitle">COLLATERAL DAMAGE AGAINST TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseAntiAircraftTitle">ANTI AIRCRAFT DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseShelterTitle">DEFENSE SHELTER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LandInvasionStrengthTitle">LAND INVASION STRENGTH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TroopsEfficiencyTitle">TROOPS EFFICIENCY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TroopsCompoundTitle">TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemRecycleTooltipEffect">PILLAGE THIS SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemRazeTooltipEffect">RAZE THIS SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ClassWeaponFleetTitle">THE WEAPON CLASS IN FLEET</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EconomicVictoryScoreTitle">ECONOMIC VICTORY POINT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticVictoryScoreTitle">DIPLOMATIC VICTORY POINT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%IsolationistBonusTitle">ISOLATIONIST BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StackCapacityMultiplierTitle">STACK CAPACITY MULTIPLIER</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GlobalFoodBonusTitle">GLOBAL FOOD BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationCostTitle">POPULATION COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CancellingBlocusMalusTitle">BLOCKADE MALUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DisharmonyMalusTitle">DISHARMONY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireDustCorruptionMalusTitle">ON DISHARMONY PENALTY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitHarmonyDustCorruptionTitle">DISHARMONY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAmoeba1TooltipEffect1">+2 $(Approval) PER % OF DIPLOMATIC VICTORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony2TooltipEffect1">+100% $(Speed) ON SHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony2TooltipEffect2">+100% $(FreeSpeed) ON SHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony1TooltipEffect1">+10% DAMAGE MAX PER ABUNDANT RESOURCE ON EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony1TooltipEffect2">+10% DAMAGE MIN PER ABUNDANT RESOURCE ON EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony1TooltipEffect3">+10% DEFENSE PER ABUNDANT RESOURCE ON EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHarmony3TooltipEffect1">+500 DEFENSE FOR EACH PLANET WITH MAX $(Population) ON PURIFIED SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho1TooltipEffect1">+3 XP PER EACH BATTLE WHILE IN INVASION BUSHIDO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho2TooltipEffect1">+25 $(Approval) ON SYSTEM WHILE IN INVASION BUSHIDO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHissho3TooltipEffect1">+5% DAMAGE FOR EACH DECLARED WAR WHILE IN INVASION BUSHIDO</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio1TooltipEffect1">+100% $(Food) ON SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio1TooltipEffect2">BONUS REDUCTION BY -2% $(Food) PER $(Population) ON EMPIRE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueHoratio2TooltipEffect1">+1 $(Approval) PER $(Population)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance1TooltipEffect1">-5% SHIP COST WHEN UNDER BLOCKADE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance1TooltipEffect2">-10% SHIP COST WHEN UNDER SIEGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance2TooltipEffect1">+5% $(FIDS) PER ENDLESS WONDER ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance2TooltipEffect2">+10 $(Approval) PER ENDLESS WONDER ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueResistance2TooltipEffect3">+5 $(Science) PER ENDLESS TEMPLE ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueAutomaton2TooltipEffect1">33% BONUS ON $(FIDS) MINUS PERCENTAGE OF ALREADY OWNED GALAXY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran2TooltipEffect1">+1% EMPIRE'S INFLUENCE ADDED TO $(Money) ON HOME SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueTerran2TooltipEffect2">+1% EMPIRE'S INFLUENCE ADDED TO $(Industry) ON HOME SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm1TooltipEffect1">-25% UPKEEP ON SHIPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm2TooltipEffect1">0.5% OF MILITARY POWER BECOMES BONUS $(Approval) ON SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm3TooltipEffect1">+5% DAMAGE PER DEPLETED PLANETS ON SHIPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueSwarm3TooltipEffect2">+5% INVASION POWER PER DEPLETED PLANETS ON SHIPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ElementConstructionEffects">CONSTRUCTION EFFECTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PositiveGrowthFactorTitle">ON POPULATION GROWTH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EvadeTitle">EVADE SCORE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemStatusSiegeTitle">SYSTEM UNDER SIEGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemVariablePopulationFrozenTitle">Your current construction is freezing the growth of your system</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HullWeaknessTitle">HULL WEAKNESS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HasRepairModuleTitle">SUPPORT MODULE (REPAIR)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassLarge1AutomatonTooltipEffect">+10% AUTO-REPAIR PER TURN WHEN Ḩ UNDER 33%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassLarge1SowerTooltipEffect">USED TONNAGE ADDED TO Ḩ ON SHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleFighterWeightBonusTitle">FIGHTERS TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleTroopsWeightBonusTitle">TROOPS TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleBomberWeightBonusTitle">BOMBERS TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleDefenseToPointDefenseTooltipEffect">25MP MODULE DEFENSE INCREASES POINT DEFENSE POWER BY 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HullWeaknessBonusTitle">HULL WEAKNESS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AccuracyBonusTitle">ACCURACY BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EvadeBonusTitle">EVADE BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombImprovementWeightBonusTitle">TONNAGE FOR BOMB TARGETING BUILDINGS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleBombPopulationWeightBonusTitle">TONNAGE FOR BOMB TARGETING POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleMissileWeightBonusTitle">FLAK MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleLaserWeightBonusTitle">SHIELD MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenseModuleKineticWeightBonusTitle">DEFLECTOR MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModulePointDefenseWeightBonusTitle">POINT DEFENSE MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SpecialModuleWeightBonusTitle">SPECIAL MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleWeightBonusTitle">SUPPORT MODULE TONNAGE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombPopulationCompoundTitle">BOMB TARGETING POPULATION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%BombImprovementCompoundTitle">BOMB TARGETING BUILDINGS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModulePowerCompoundTitle">SUPPORT MODULE (POWER)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SupportModuleCivilianCompoundTitle">SUPPORT MODULE (CIVILIAN)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialPointDefense1GenericEffect1">3 SHOTS PER ROUND / DAMAGE DEPENDING ON SHIP'S DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TroopsPopulationCostAdditiveValueTitle">INCREMENTAL POPULATION COST OF TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TroopsPopulationCostFactorTitle">POPULATION COST FACTOR OF TROOPS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EconomicVictoryProgressionHundredTitle">% OF ECONOMIC VICTORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticVictoryProgressionHundredTitle">% OF DIPLOMATIC VICTORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemVariableMoneyNetHarmonyDescription">Dust was the Harmony's downfall. They see it as a menace and a plague, and no source of Dust production will be tolerated on any Harmony star system.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireVariableMoneyHarmonyDescription">The intergalactic currency is "Dust", a rare resource left from the time of the Endless. As it is the reason for the chaos within the Harmony civilization, they would rather destroy it than use it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyBonus3HarmonyTooltipEffect">TRADE ROUTES GENERATES $(Food) INSTEAD OF $(Money)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TemporaryEffectsTooltipEffect">TEMPORARY EFFECTS, DEPENDING ON THE GAME SPEED:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassTitle">BUILDING SHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateFighter.MeleeTitle">DURING DOG FIGHTS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateFighter.ChasingTitle">WHEN BOMBERS CHASING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateFighter.OnShipTitle">DURING SHIP ASSAULT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateFighter.ReturningToHangarTitle">WHEN RETURNING TO HANGAR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateBomber.MovingToShipTitle">DURING SHIP APPROACH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateBomber.OnShipTitle">DURING SHIP ASSAULT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StateBomber.ReturningToHangarTitle">WHEN RETURNING TO HANGAR</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DamagePerShotTitle">DAMAGE PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%QuantityTitle">TINY SHIPS PER SQUAD</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShotsPerRoundTitle">SHOTS PER ROUND</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementConstructionTitle">IMPROVEMENTS' CONSTRUCTION</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ImprovementFixedTurnsBonusTitle">TURN-FIXED DURATION OF AN IMPROVEMENT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DestroyedShipCategory">DESTROYED SHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DestroyedShipDescription">The black box from this ship was partially damaged in combat or the system itself was a victim of cyber-sabotage. Data retrieved will not be 100% accurate.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DestroyedEvacuationShipCategory">DESTROYED SHIP</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DestroyedEvacuationShipDescription">The black box from this ship was partially damaged in combat or the system itself was a victim of cyber-sabotage. Data retrieved will not be 100% accurate.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHisshoTooltipEffect2">       • +5% WEAPON DAMAGE ON ALL FLEETS FOR EACH SPACE BATTLE WON (FOR 15 TURNS).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHisshoTooltipEffect3">
       • +20% FID ON ALL SYSTEMS FOR EACH INVASION VICTORY (FOR 10 TURNS).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RallyPointDestinationTitle">RALLY POINT TO $System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%RallyPointEditModeTitle">RALLY POINT SETTING MODE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ResourceDepositStrategicTitle">STRATEGIC RESOURCE DEPOSIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HarmonyBonusTitle">RESTORATION GRIDS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoneyToConvertTitle">CONVERTED DUST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HarmonyOrbitingBonusFactorTitle">RESONANT VESSELS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HarmonyMaxOrbitingBonusFactorTitle">RESONANT VESSELS MAX BONUS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TOOLTIPEFFECTS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTooltipEffect5">
+2 FIS PER SHIP ORBITING COLONIZED SYSTEM. LIMITED TO 2x MAX ḧ.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityHarmonyTooltipEffect6" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponFakeTooltipEffect0">UNLOCKS A WEAPON MODULE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponFakeTooltipEffect1">EFFECTS DEPENDING ON THE CHOSEN SPECIALIZATION:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect1">COST: 4 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 4-8</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 15</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 1-2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 25-60</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic1TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 50-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect1">COST: 12 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 6-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 75</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 1-2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 62-180</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic2TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 50-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect1">COST: 36 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 8-12</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 210</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 1-2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 8-150</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponKinetic3TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 50-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect1">COST: 4 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 8-12</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 15</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 136-390</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 14-28</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile1TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 50-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect1">COST: 12 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 10-14</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 75</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 408-1170</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 24-48</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile2TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 50-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect1">COST: 36 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 12-16</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 210</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 816-2340</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 48-96</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponMissile3TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 50-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect1">COST: 4 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 6-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 15</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 45-103</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser1TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 60-110%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect1">COST: 12 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 8-12</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 75</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 135-310</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser2TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 60-110%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect1">COST: 36 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 10-14</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect3">$(MilitaryPower): 210</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 270-621</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect5">CRITIC MULTIPLIER: x2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect6">CRITIC CHANCE: 0.0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect7">INTERCEPTION EVASION: 0</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect8">PROJECTILES PER SALVO: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect9">ROUND(S) BEFORE REACH: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect10">ROUND(S) TO RELOAD: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleWeaponLaser3TooltipEffect11">ACCURACY: 60-110%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighterFakeTooltipEffect0">UNLOCKS A FIGHTER MODULE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighterFakeTooltipEffect1">EFFECTS DEPENDING ON THE CHOSEN SPECIALIZATION:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect1">COST: 52 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 15+10%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 1-2 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 70%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 3-7</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 33%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 15-45</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 0-150</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter1TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 0-250</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect1">COST: 104 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 20+10%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 1-2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 3-10 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 90%-100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 20%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 3-7</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 0-200</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter2TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 0-350</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect1">COST: 104 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 30+10%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 15-20 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 60%-80%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 2-3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 10%-20%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 160</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 0-300</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter3TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 0-300</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect1">COST: 260 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 45+10%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 15-50 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 80%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 1-7</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 45%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect8">Ḩ: 200-450</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 100-500</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialFighter4TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 0-750</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomberFakeTooltipEffect0">UNLOCKS A BOMBER MODULE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomberFakeTooltipEffect1">EFFECTS DEPENDING ON THE CHOSEN SPECIALIZATION:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect1">COST: 70,2 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 20+15%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 40 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 70%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 1-3</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 10%-30%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 200-300</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 80-240</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber1TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 50-400</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect1">COST: 143 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 30+15%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 9-11 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 70%-90%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 2-5</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 50%-70%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 400-700</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 50-250</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber2TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 100-600</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect1">COST: 143 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 40+15%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 60-80 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 100%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 5-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 0%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 30-60</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 0-200</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber3TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 0-300</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect1">COST: 351 $(Industry) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect2">$(Weight): 40+15%$(Weight)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect3">SLOTS: 2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect4">DAMAGE: 160 PER SHOT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect5">ACCURACY: 70%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect6">SHOTS PER ROUND: 5-15</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect7">EVADE: 30%</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect8">Ḩ : 350-600</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect9">INVASION STRENGTH: 400-900</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSpecialBomber4TooltipEffect10">LAND INVASION: 400-1100</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MODULES_TOOLTIPEFFECTS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedTitle">EMPIRE VIEW HARMONY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem0">The empire view is slightly different when playing the Harmony faction. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem1">As Harmony your Dust treasury is set to 0 and will remain this way due to their aversion for this resource.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem2">As sentient rocks they have no concept of Approval. Population growth, production and research will continue without any issues of Approval or morale.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem3">Increasing your Conversion rate will also increase your Science production, but will reduce your Food production. Reducing the Conversion rate will have the opposite effect.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem4">The Harmony need only 3 Luxury or Strategic Resources to obtain an Abundance bonus.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem5">As a consequence of their Dust intolerance, Harmony cannot buyout construction, but do not have upkeep costs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEmpireViewXp1ContinuedItem6">The Harmony do not see any interest in hiring heroes corrupted by Dust and thus will not hire them for fleets or systems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1Item4">Special slots are required to build the special modules, and their availability depends on the type of hull. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1Item5">As you progress in the game, you will discover new modules to install in your ships. Use these tabs to switch between the families of modules: Weapon and Defense, Support, and Special.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1Item6">To add or remove a module on a ship, simply click on + or - symbols in the “Available Modules” area.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1Item7">Some categories may have several module options depending on range or specialization. This is trye for weapons as well as for special modules.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1Item0">Module status is shown as follows:</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1ContinuedItem1">A module which has not been researched will be disabled (grey). </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1ContinuedItem2">Adding a module will be impossible if the weight of that module exceeds the remaining tonnage capacity or, as in this case, if the module requires access to a Strategic Resource.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1ContinuedItem3">A module included in the ship design is highlighted with a blue frame. The quantity of that module is displayed in the bottom-right of that area.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1ContinuedItem4">The ship area summarizes within each category box The modules currently selected for the Ship Design are summarized within each category box.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialShipDesignViewXp1ContinuedItem5">Some modules can be damaged. Their repair rate depends on the system their ship is orbiting (own or ally).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialFleetControlXp1Item6">The Invasion action triggers a siege to conquer an enemy's system. You will also have the choice to send bombs or land troops in order to speed your invasion (if you have enough power and the proper modules are installed) </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialMilitaryViewXp1Item6">Use the Retrofit button to upgrade Ships or entire fleets to the latest revision of their Ship Design. This will cost you some Dust. Note that the Harmony cannot use this. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialSystemViewXp1ContinuedItem5">You can assign a Hero to govern a Star System (unless you are playing Harmony faction). Depending on their specializations, the Hero can provide bonuses in things like production output, defense, etc.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialBattleViewItem7Xp1">You can select a Targeting Action for the following combat phase.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialBattleViewItem8Xp1">Your Fleet Formation is displayed here.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialBattleViewItem9Xp1">You can hide the interface. Click on the  "H" key to show it again.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialBattleViewItem10Xp1">These are camera buttons. The first one allows you to control the camera using your mouse and the arrows on your keyboard. The second allows you to follow a squadron of fighters or bombers if any are in the fleet. Use the arrow keys to switch between them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEncounterPanelXp1Item6">You can pre-select a Target strategy for the first and following phases.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEncounterPanelXp1Item7">You can pre-select a Fleet Formation for the duration of the combat.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEncounterPanelReportXp1Item6">The first column displays how much damage you inflicted on the enemy as well as the average efficiency of the enemy's defenses as a percentage (how much damage passed through the enemy defenses or was stopped by them).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TutorialEncounterPanelReportXp1Item7">The last column is the opposite, showing how much damage the enemy inflicted on you, and how efficient your defenses and weapons were. Analyzing offensive and defensive stats will allow you to optimize your ship designs to better defeat your enemies.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TUTORIAL" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony01">The Harmony were born at the same moment as the universe.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony02">As old as time, they traversed the galaxies,</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony03">... seeking the mysterious confluence of galactic rhythms they call The Core.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony04">But that changed forever when they encountered Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony05">From a movement to a series of individuals, from a sense of the Core to a</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony06">sense of loss, the Harmony are no longer what they were.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony07">But they remember what happened, and will never renounce</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesHarmony08">... their relentless war against the Dust that corrupted them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters01">Space is deep, dark,</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters02">and dangerous. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters03">But then, so are we.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters04">We have risen and fallen,</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters05">learned to adapt and rebuild, </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters06">for our history </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters07">is a history of struggle and survival.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters08">We protect our own. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters09">We take what we need, </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters10">and salvage what we find.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters11">To be a Vaulter is to work hard, </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters12">fight hard, </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters13">and celebrate hard. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters14">Because life is hard.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters15">But it is also beautiful, </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters16">and even in the deep dark of space, </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SubtitlesVaulters17">it never fails to give us hope.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_SUBTITLES" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_CREDITS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MODDING" />
</Datatable>