<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_OUTGAME" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionNameVauTitle">VAULTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionNameVauDescription">An ancient, nomadic people that have had a galactic run of bad luck, Vaulters are humanoids who are skilled in science and defensive warfare.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionNameVaulterDescription">An ancient, nomadic people that have had a galactic run of bad luck, Vaulters are humanoids who are skilled in science and defensive warfare.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionVauDescription">Home Planet Type: Terran
Diplomatic Alignment: Neutral
Gameplay: Defense, Science
Main Victory Type: Scientific
 
An ancient faction, the Vaulters have suffered a number of major setbacks in trying to establish a permanent home for themselves. Though characterized as restless wanderers, they are in fact a proud and adaptable race, seeking a system that they can finally call 'home.' Their centuries of travel and tinkering have made them skilled at both science and warfare, though their greatest military strength is in defense.

The Vaulters have an old tradition of appointing female leaders, and their trust in this tradition has been confirmed by the faction's uncanny ability to escape, survive, and live to fight another day. Once based on the planet Auriga, they left the planet when their predictions indicated potentially cataclysmic geo-atmospheric problems. Their attempts to colonize elsewhere have only had brief success, and the notion of a permanent base has gained an almost mythical status.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience04Title">FACTION TRAIT</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience04NormTitle">Kitchen Chemists</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TraitScience04NormDescription">A nation of tinkers and hobbyists, scientific experimentation is done everywhere and all the time. Scorched eyebrows and billows of smoke are common sights.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityVaulterTitle">Vaulter Affinity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityVaulterDescription">Provides a basic set of faction traits similar to the Vaulters (Science/Defence, Fleet teleportation)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityVaulterTooltipEffect1">ONCE CONSTRUCTED, THE PORTAL CONSUMES ALL REMAINING MOVEMENT POINTS WHEN USED.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityVaulterTooltipEffect2">REQUIRES AT LEAST ONE MOVEMENT POINT.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityMappingVaulterTitle">Vaulters Appearance</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityMappingVaulterDescription">Your custom faction will display the 2D and 3D visuals of the Vaulters.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_FACTION" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_OPTIONS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_GEN" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_GAMEMENU" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TOOLTIP" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_GALAXY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueVaulter1Title">ADVANCED APERTURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueVaulter1Description">The use of the system portals consumes 75% of Ḡ instead of all remaining Ḡ. At least one movement point is still required.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueVaulter2Title">EXTENDED BUNKERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueVaulter2Description">Part of the diplomatic deal with allied nations is the local installation of Vaulter mini-bunkers. Ostensibly for defense and supply, in reality they are miniature "pocket" portals  running real-time galaxy-wide data exchanges. Communicating via these bunkers gives a major information advantage to Vaulter fleets in allied territory.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueVaulter3Title">ALLIED C3 SYSTEMS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUniqueVaulter3Description">Using the latest advances in military technology, Vaulters integrate their own battlefield communications systems with those of allied factions. The result gives them a major bonus when planning offensive or defensive operations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_EMPIRE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_SYSTEM" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_RESEARCH" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_PLANET" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TECHSYSTEM" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TECHPLANET" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE04VaulterTitle">EFFICIENT SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE04VaulterDescription">By augmenting the natural magnetic characteristics of the hull material and using lighter alloys in construction, this improved ship design gives bonuses to tonnage and improves kinetic and missile defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE08VaulterTitle">BARYONIC SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE08VaulterDescription">While there are some particles that can pass through plasma shielding, this improved version prevents penetration by any baryon particle (primarily neutrons and protons).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE14VaulterTitle">APPLIED ATMOSPHERICS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE14VaulterDescription">A great deal of practical engineering for ships can be learned from atmospheric sciences. In particular, streamlined and efficient ventilation systems as well as more advanced magnetic and thermodynamic models all aid in creating next-generation ships </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE16VaulterTitle">NON-BARYONIC SHIELDING</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE16VaulterDescription">Non-baryonic particles had long been the great mystery of advanced physics. Now, a greater understanding of the nature and mechanics of particles such as photons, gravitons, and anti-matter permits the creation of shielding systems that either repel or contain non-baryonic matter.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA19VaulterTitle">DEFCON INCUBATORS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA19VaulterDescription">These are specialized incubators for Vaulter entrepreneurs who want to create defense-oriented technology start-ups. The companies receive privileged access to the latest scientific research, and in turn generate both improved technologies and better gear for allied units.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG05VaulterTitle">MILITARY-ARTISANAL COMPLEX</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG05VaulterDescription">A new theory in the development of complex societies, it turns much manufacturing theory on its head. Essentially, the use of highly coupled, massively on-line individual machine shops permits highly efficient local industry while maintaining the benefits of large-scale, standardized products.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG11VaulterTitle">NEURO-COUPLED DATA</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG11VaulterDescription">One of the things discovered as a branch development of the Vaulter portal technology is the ability to directly 'feed' data into complex electrical networks -- including the brain. While extended sessions can be exhausting or even life-threatening, it provides an efficient way to rapidly disseminate large amounts of information to many learners.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG19VaulterTitle">STEALTH SATELLITES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG19VaulterDescription">Extending their technology to autonomous semi-permanent portals, Vaulter scientists have created satellites that share vast volumes of data instantaneously across great distances. They power up and down in micro-seconds, thus maintaining near-zero levels of radiation.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG65VaulterTitle">"POCKET" PORTAL TECH</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechG65VaulterDescription">Used to doing more with less, Vaulter scientists have devised miniaturized portal systems. Rather than transferring objects, they act as an instantaneous communication web that keeps Vaulter fleets across the galaxy in touch with each other.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE37VaulterTitle">NATURAL APERTURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechE37VaulterDescription">The discovery of naturaly-occurring weak points in the fabric of time-space has allowed a great leap in the use of portal transport. By building or re-aligning portals according to locations where objects more easily slip between dimensions, the energy cost of portal travel is greatly reduced.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA28VaulterTitle">SUB-QUANTUM CALORIMETERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TechA28VaulterDescription">An inevitable advance from traditional, semi-conductor based particle detection, these new "Advanced Nosfer" systems capture data from a wide range of inputs - quantum perturbations, dark matter interactions, and time-reversed polarity inflected anti-matter.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TECHTREE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_BATTLE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterColonizationTitle">Nadjne</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterColonizationDescription">Role: Colonization</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterSmall1Title">Anjka</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterSmall1Description">Role: Exploration/Multiple
Generally an explorer-class ship, named for a famed Vaulter explorer who discovered their previous home planet, Orrin.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterSmall2Title">Ylona</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterSmall2Description">Role: Multiple
A ship that has an advantage when loading weapon modules, it is named for the warrior leader who coined the Vaulter phrase "Glory benefits one; survival, all."</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterMedium1Title">Ljdya</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterMedium1Description">Role: Multiple
Designed for large engines and heavy armor, this class of Vaulter ship is named for the leader who maintained the defensive capabilities of four vulnerable spatial platforms during the War of the Broken Skies.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterMedium2Title">Erszebet</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterMedium2Description">Role: Defense/Multiple
Reliable, dependable, and oriented towards defense, this ship class is an all-round performer. It is named after a Vaulter hero who perished leading the rearguard when the Vaulter clans were driven from Orrin .</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterLarge1Title">Yldjko</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipClassVaulterLarge1Description">Role: Multiple
Large, heavy, and dangerous, this class of ship is nicknamed for the famous "Rock of the Eyrie." While stories of her exploits on Auriga are legendary, it is little known how much of that is fact and how much is fiction.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassVaulterSmall1Title">Anjka</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassVaulterSmall2Title">Ylona</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassVaulterMedium1Title">Ljdya</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassVaulterMedium2Title">Erszebet</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%InvasionShipClassVaulterLarge1Title">Yldjko</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ColonyShipVaulterDesign">Clanship</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AdvancedDefenderVaulterDesign">Valkyr Matriarch</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%SuperDefenderVaulterDesign">Super Valkyr</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DefenderVaulterDesign">Valkyr</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ScoutVaulterDesign">Probe</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_SHIP" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_FLEET" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero81LastName">Tenekech</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero81FirstName1">Attjla</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero81Description">Tenekech is aware of the fact that he is a direct-line descendent of Anjka, but he doesn't rub it in. Good-humored, loud, and happy, his jolly exterior hides a clever mind and some of the nimblest fingers in the fleet. Like most Vaulters he dreams of a permanent home, and his famous ancestor's renown makes it even more important for him.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Hero81FlavorText" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_HERO" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MODULE" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCeaseFireTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">Resources should be hoarded, not wasted in war. A Cease Fire seems acceptable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCeaseFireTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">I think we've made our point, and I don't think war is the way to move ahead. The clans are fine with a Cease Fire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">Things aren't going the way we want them to. Maybe a Cooperation Agreement would help change that.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">We have a stable base to work from. Let's try a Cooperation Agreement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">We're moving in the right direction and we could speed that up with a Cooperation Agreement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCreateAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">I'm going against the opinions of some of the clans when I offer this. Don't make me regret it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCreateAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">An Alliance isn't like being pregnant. You can always back out if you decide it's a bad idea.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingCreateAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">I'm feeling like you're people we can work with. Enough, in fact, to cement this with an Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingDeclareWarTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">This galaxy isn't somewhere we can both live in peace. Let's clean this up the hard way.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingDeclareWarTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">Too bad for all of us, but this is how it works out. The clans will close ranks and raise shields.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingDeclareWarTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">Things were looking better, but not good enough. If we want this to go our way, it'll take blood and pain.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">Hope is running dry, luck is running out. But maybe if you join our Alliance, we can fix that.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">There may be some advantages in bringing you into our clans. What do you say?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">We have something we can nurture and build on. What do you say you join our Alliance?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">There's a shortage of trust between us; this won't last. We're asking you to leave the Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">The future is never sure. But however it goes, we don't see you being part of this Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">Even if things are improving, prospects just don't appear to be that fertile. We want you out of the Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingPeaceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">We've been living without a Peace Treaty for too long. Relations may not be great, but the clans would prefer the stability of a peace. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingPeaceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">Could be better, could be worse. Overall, we'd like to formalize this with a Peace Treaty and use our resources more productively.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingPeaceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">Everyone gets hungry - or hungrier - in wars and cease fires. We're thinking we can trust you enough to offer a Peace Treaty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOpenBordersTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">As scarce as trust is these days, we're still ready to propose Open Borders with you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOpenBordersTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">We'd like to settle down and settle our differences. Are you ready to go ahead and risk Open Borders?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOpenBordersTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">I say we build something together. We're willing to try Open Borders if you'll do the same. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOtherTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">I wouldn't trust you to babysit, but maybe we can still come to a deal that's good for both of us.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOtherTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">We're holding things together with band-aids and baling wire here. Maybe we could help each other out.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIOfferingOtherTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">There's a lot of risk and instability out there. The clans are willing to offer you this deal and stabilize things a bit.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermVaulterLeft">We don't believe in death before dishonor, but we'll still take it over rash stupidity. The answer is "No".</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermVaulterMidLeft">We've been living in war this long; we're willing to dig in a little longer unless you sweeten the deal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermVaulterMidRight">We have machines to repair and wounds to heal. Your proposal doesn't sound half bad.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCeaseFireTermVaulterRight">We're ready to turn from ruining crops to raising them. I like the way your offer sounds.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterLeft">The clans would sooner leave a pack of wolves to watch the nursery.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterMidLeft">Lots of things are scarce right now, and one of them is trust. Sorry, no deal.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterMidRight">We've been trying to do too many things with too little help. A little cooperation might not be a bad move.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCooperationAgreementTermVaulterRight">We like where we are; the clans are ready to put down some roots. A Cooperation Agreement sounds just fine.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermVaulterLeft">We'd have to be hungry and terrified to join that Alliance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermVaulterMidLeft">We don't have the kind of relations we can build that base on. We're not ready to join you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermVaulterMidRight">We need a little more of everything, and an Alliance might just help us get there.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingCreateAllianceTermVaulterRight">We're hoping we've found a permanent home for the clans, and we'd be glad to have you as neighbors.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterLeft">So you say it's time to kill people and break things? Be careful what you ask for.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterMidLeft">More blood and destruction, is it? We're not happy, but the clans are ready.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterMidRight">We are surprised that this is how you react to the situation. But we're always prepared for the worst.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterRight">War is unfortunate; both on principle and with you. But if it is war you want, you'll find our bunkers are deep and our storehouses full.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">We felt the stock of good will running low. This is unfortunate, but hardly shocking.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">Too bad. We thought that relations were on an even keel, not a downward spiral. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingDeclareWarTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">This is not the best time to go to war with you, but there's no good time for that.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterLeft">Alliances, like births, are delicate beginnings. But this baby doesn't have a chance.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterMidLeft">It's nice to know that an Alliance is in your interest, but it doesn't quite appear to be in ours.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterMidRight">An Alliance is a promising improvement; the history of our clans tells us that mutual support is key to survival.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingInviteToAllianceTermVaulterRight">We won't hide the fact that we are in favor of this Alliance. The clans are ready to work with you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterLeft">If you hadn't suggested this, we probably would have done it ourselves.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterMidLeft">I suppose that is the way things are headed, though we had hopes for improvement.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterMidRight">We'll survive in spite of this; the clans always do. But to be honest, we're a little surprised.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterRight">How can this be possible? We thought you were a serious people.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendWorsening">Our relations were decaying; whatever we had hoped to build was dying anyway.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendStable">We thought that relations were balanced; apparently you did not.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingLeaveAllianceTermVaulterAttitudeTrendImproving">This is a serious proposal? It's not good to break and ruin something that's going well.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermVaulterLeft">Our minds are as good as our defenses. You won't dupe the clans into a lopsided peace.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermVaulterMidLeft">We are not prepared to lower our defenses to you. Not yet. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermVaulterMidRight">Peace can bring opportunities that war does not. We are ready for a change.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingPeaceTermVaulterRight">We like the way you think. The benefits of peace will help us all grow.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermVaulterLeft">The clans rarely let people inside our defenses, and if we did it sure as hell wouldn't be you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermVaulterMidLeft">We're not lowering our guard for that. Open Borders requires more trust that you've earned.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermVaulterMidRight">We'll agree to Open Borders, though not all of the clans are in favor. We'll see how it goes.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOpenBordersTermVaulterRight">We trust you enough to let you inside our defenses -- I wonder if you understand what that means.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermVaulterLeft">Is this an attempt to show a sense of humor?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermVaulterMidLeft">We don't see an advantage in this deal, and we don't make deals just for entertainment.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermVaulterMidRight">You seem to be reasonable, and this offer seems to make sense. We'll go with it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomaticAnswersAIRespondingOtherTermVaulterRight">We wouldn't be taking the good of our clans seriously if we said "No" to this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyStatusAllianceDescription">You are in an alliance with this empire, sharing all decisions to declare peace and war on other empires. You can see each others' systems and travel freely within them. Note: An alliance allows use of Vaulter Portals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyOpenBordersTermDescription">This will allow the empire to navigate freely in your territories (requires Peace). Note: This allows use of Vaulter Portals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyCreateAllianceTermDescription">This will propose to the contacted empire that you form an alliance together.  Note: This allows use of Vaulter Portals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DiplomacyInviteToAllianceTermDescription">This will offer the contacted empire to join your alliance.  Note: This allows use of Vaulter Portals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_DIPLOMACY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_EVENTOVERLAY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MILITARY" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MESSAGES" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience4VaulterTitle">DEFCON INCUBATORS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience4VaulterDescription">These are specialized incubators for Vaulter entrepreneurs who want to create defense-oriented technology start-ups. These companies receive privileged access to the latest scientific discoveries  in order to create new systems and weapons for military purposes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience4VaulterTooltipEffect">50% OF ḗ ADDED TO SYSTEM DEFENSE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense1VaulterTitle">ADAPTATION CENTERS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense1VaulterDescription">While these centers are designed to study new planets and help Vaulter settlers adapt to them, like every Vaulter infrastructure they include defensive turrets, bunkers, and warehouses. The research that goes on within is equally defense-oriented, and helps Vaulter settlers dig in to new planets and convert them into strongly defended bases</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense1VaulterTooltipEffect1">+5  ḗ PER PLANET COLONIZED ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense2VaulterTitle">INSURGENCY ACADEMIES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense2VaulterDescription">As the Vaulters are a people that have a long history of adapting to survive, a fundamental part of their education includes how to create defensive structures and weapons regardless of the local technology, biology, and geology. Training civilians and warriors to be dangerous with everyday tools improves both defense and everyday scientific knowledge</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense2VaulterTooltipEffect2">+1 ḗ PER POP ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense3VaulterTitle">REACTIVE BEACONS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense3VaulterDescription">When Vaulters have settled a system, they naturally and automatically think about how to improve its defences. This ring of probes and satellites, communicating and reacting in real time, provides superior information and coordination to Vaulter defensive units</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDefense3VaulterTooltipEffect3">+5%  ḗ ON SYSTEM</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementVaulterPortalTitle">VAULTER APERTURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementVaulterPortalDescription">The faction can instantly teleport a Fleet from one system to another system that is under their influence, if both systems have built these portals.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementVaulterPortalTooltipEffect1">FLEET TELEPORT BETWEEN SYSTEMS WITH PORTALS. ALL MOVEMENT POINTS CONSUMED.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementVaulterPortalTooltipEffect2">PORTAL CONSTRUCTION ELIMINATES EXPANSION DISAPPROVAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementVaulterPortalTooltipEffect3">MUST HAVE 100% CONTROL OF SYSTEM TO BUILD PORTAL</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueVaulterTitle">PORTAL PARTICLE SCREENS</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueVaulterDescription">Strange things happen to matter and time when they are accelerated and teleported via the Vaulter Aperture portals. By installing screening systems that read the sub-atomic particles generated in portal exchanges, Vaulter scientists learn a great deal about time, the universe, and high-risk mass transit.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TeleportationMovementCostFactorTitle">TELEPORTATION MOVEMENT COST</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%CanUseTeleportationPortalsTitle">USE OF VAULTER PORTALS PERMITTED</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%TeleportationPortalTitle">VAULTER APERTURE</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AlliedTerritoryAttackBonusTitle">DAMAGE WHEN FIGHTING ON ALLIED TERRITORY</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VaulterPortalBonusOnScienceTitle">BONUS FROM CONSTRUCTED APERTURES</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueVaulterTooltipEffect1">LINKS THE PORTALS TO PROVIDE + 1% ḗ PER  CONSTRUCTED APERTURE.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueVaulterTooltipEffect2">ONE-TIME BONUS (NOT AFFECTED BY ADDITIONAL IMPROVEMENTS, NOT CUMULATIVE)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TOOLTIPEFFECTS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MODULES_TOOLTIPEFFECTS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_TUTORIAL" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_SUBTITLES" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_CREDITS" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%Dummy_MODDING" />
</Datatable>